[{"value": {"id": 1818504, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64330", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps he has taken to develop relations between the UK Government and the European Union.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4479, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "answerText": "At the first UK-EU Summit held on 19 May, the Government agreed a substantial package to take forward our future partnership. The Government will now move forward to begin negotiations to conclude as swiftly as possible. We will keep Parliament updated on...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Relations with EU", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819368, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment  she has made of the effectiveness of the probation service in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819367, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of prisons in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819366, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations has he made to his Israeli counterpart on the humanitarian situation in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819365, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the 10 Year Health Plan for England on the Black Country.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819364, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64969", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of mandating DBS checks for people who wish to stand for election.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819359, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64968", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to help reduce violence against women and girls in the West Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819357, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-17T00:00:00", "uin": "64967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that lessons learned from the COVID-19 Vaccine Taskforce will inform its approach to managing the shortages of pancreatic enzyme replacement therapy (PERT).", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819356, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64966", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to help end discrimination against the trans community.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819355, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-17T00:00:00", "uin": "64965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has conducted a 360-degree supply and demand forecast for pancreatic enzyme replacement therapy to assess the long-term needs for patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819354, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64964", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to ensure the safety of girls and young women in public places.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819353, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64963", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps is she taking to tackle misogyny against girls and young women.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819352, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the post- (a) 16 and (b) 18 support for young people raised in kinship.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819351, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the trends in the levels of ambulance callouts to the same patient more than once in a 24 hour period.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819349, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve ambulance response times in (a) Surrey and (b) Hampshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819348, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64959", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of oral nicotine pouches on public health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819347, "askingMemberId": 5244, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what role will organically certified produce have in achieving 50 percent of public sector catering contracts from British producers or those certified to higher environmental standard", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819346, "askingMemberId": 5355, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the requirement that (a) all and (b) terminally ill patients should renew their Medical Exemption Certificates every five year", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819345, "askingMemberId": 5355, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of data protection laws in ensuring that legitimate complaints processes are dealt with effectively by health bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819344, "askingMemberId": 5290, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her plan is for the next phase of free breakfast club provision in primary schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819343, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact Avanti West Coast\u2019s non-tilting 110mph (a) Class 805 and (b) Class 807 trains on the capacity of the West Coast Main Line.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819342, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of (a) free breakfast clubs and (b) the free school meal expansion on poverty in North Northumberland constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819341, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department considers future demographic changes when planning school funding.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819340, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to support adult social care in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819339, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the NHS is prepared for future demographic changes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819338, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the 10 year plan on older residents in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819337, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64948", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many additional GPs have been hired in North Northumberland constituency through Government funding.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819336, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the 10-year plan on waiting lists in the North East.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819335, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64946", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of reducing the rates for Extended Producer Responsibility fees for more recyclable materials.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819334, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64945", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of basing the calculation of Extended Producer Responsibility fees on volume.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819333, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64944", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of a reduction on the savings limit on Individual Savings Accounts on savers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819332, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64943", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2025 to Question 56485 on Children: Maintenance, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of aligning the child maintenance responsibilities of those who rec", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819331, "askingMemberId": 5281, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will publish an economic impact assessment on the potential impact of the National Insurance exemption for Indian nationals posted temporarily to the UK under the UK\u2013India Free Trade Agreement on", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819330, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64941", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using artificial intelligence in the regulatory process for short-term lets.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819329, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many full-time equivalent staff will be needed to enforce the short-term lets database.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819328, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department's consultation outcome entitled Consultation on a registration scheme for short-term lets in England, updated on 19 July 2024, when she will publish a full respon", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819327, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64938", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the tax revenue from ensuring compliance with rules on eligibility of short-term lets for business rates.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819326, "askingMemberId": 5241, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the Civil Aviation Authority's requirement that commercial pilots cease commercial air transport operations at the age of 65, regardless of (a) medical condition ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819325, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Scottish Government on improving mental health resources for (a) nurses and (b) other medical care providers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819324, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to increase the powers of (a) enforcement and (b) collection of the Child Maintenance Service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819323, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the collection of late payments by the Child Maintenance Service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819322, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64933", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to simplify early years funding for parents and guardians.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819321, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Highways England's roadside litter clearing duties.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819320, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to help mitigate the environmental impacts of AI data centres in relation to the target of Net Zero by 2050.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819319, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of social prescribing on (a) reducing GP appointments and (b) improving patient wellbeing in (i) mental health and (ii) social isolation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819318, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to further integrate social prescribing into the Neighbourhood Health model.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819317, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support (a) voluntary and (b) community sector organisations delivering social prescribing services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819316, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of paragraph 129 of the First Report of the Housing, Communities and Local Government Committee of S", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819315, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she is taking steps to amend the local plan process to (a) include a stronger needs assessment for social housing across the plan period and (b) require local authorities", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819314, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to set up an independent body to process Disclosure and Barring Service checks with formalised processing time targets.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819313, "askingMemberId": 5327, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64924", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding was allocated for preparations for the 2031 census in each of the past three financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819372, "askingMemberId": 5062, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what basis Serco can refuse to inform Members of Parliament when (a) houses, (b) hotels and (c) other premises are being used for asylum dispersal in their constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819371, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with colleagues in the Department for Transport on the potential impact of access to public transport on access to healthcare.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819370, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients who live in England and treated in Wales are impacted by changes to NHS organisation in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819369, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of differing NHS (a) targets and (b) waiting lists in England and Wales on patients living in border communities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819363, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64919", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will require the National Security Adviser to publish details of meetings with external organisations other than senior media executives.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819362, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 62768 on Pay: Publicity, what the aggregate value was of the payments to the six digital influencers; and if he will name those influencers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819361, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 62346 on Postage Stamps, whether his Department hold copies of the (a) agenda (b) minutes and (c) papers of the Royal Mail\u2019s stamp advisory committee.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819360, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the cancellation of the communications campaign entitled, Better Health - Every Mind Matters: Loneliness, on mental health outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819358, "askingMemberId": 5039, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) support research into (i) Sudden Unexpected Death in Epilepsy (SUDEP) and (ii) epilepsy-related mortality, (b) improve understanding of the causes of thos", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819350, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued on whether applicants for (a) leave to remain and (b) fee waiver who have (i) had their claims rejected, (ii) lost their right to work, (iii) lost their access ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819311, "askingMemberId": 4651, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the national inquiry into group-based child sexual exploitation is (a) independent and (b) led by survivors.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819310, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Draft Enterprise Act 2002 (Mergers Involving Newspaper Enterprises and Foreign Powers) Regulations 2025, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the partial owner", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819309, "askingMemberId": 5145, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether the forthcoming roadmap to phase out animal testing include plans to conduct systematic reviews to identify areas of research or disease models to phase out.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819301, "askingMemberId": 5190, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64910", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Infected Blood Compensation Authority plans to prioritise older claimants when making payments.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819295, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Palestinian nationals have entered the UK under (a) humanitarian and (b) asylum schemes since October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819294, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what support her Department provides to local authorities to (a) build and (b) maintain sports facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819293, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure pupils are able to access high quality meals in schools in (a) Eastbourne and (b) the South East.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819292, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the press release of 15 May 2025 entitled Media law reforms to boost press sustainability and protect independence, whether a company (a) wholly owned by and (b) under the major", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819291, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support veterans in (a) Eastbourne and (b) the South East.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819290, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department plans to take to support the development of padel courts in Eastleigh constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819289, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help improve levels of digital literacy in the South East.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819288, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans her Department has to (a) reduce pavement parking and (b) encourage the removal of obstacles for pedestrians with visual impairments.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819287, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of renewing the Air Tanker refuelling contract, in the context of the agreement to buy 12 F-35A jets.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819286, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help grow the tourism industry in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819285, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support music and arts programmes in (a) Eastbourne and (b) England.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819284, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-09T00:00:00", "uin": "64898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2025 to Question 63964 on India: F-35 Aircraft, how many personnel have been required to recover the F-35B from India; and what the cost to the public purse was for removing the w", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819282, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support grassroots sports clubs in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819281, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the enforcement of orders requiring dogs to be muzzled in public.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819280, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support libraries in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819279, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the monitoring of orders requiring dogs to be muzzled in public.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819278, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to (a) reduce the number of empty retail units and (b) help regenerate high streets in (i) Eastbourne and (ii) other towns.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819277, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many employers in Eastbourne accessed apprenticeship levy funds in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819276, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64891", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to support the uptake of apprenticeships in (a) Eastbourne and (b) East Sussex.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819275, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of penalties in place for dog-on-dog attacks involving service dogs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819274, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of protections in place to prevent service dogs from attacks by other dogs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819273, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help tackle health inequalities in (a) Eastbourne and (b) the South East.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819272, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect service dogs from attacks by other dogs.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819271, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2025 to Question 62858 on HMS Protector: Atlantic Ocean, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the modernisation of the Russian submarine fleet on national securi", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819270, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to improve access to reproductive health in (a) Eastbourne and (b) East Sussex.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819269, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the UK fashion industry\u2019s contribution to (a) economic growth and (b) employment in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819268, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, steps his Department is taking to support patients with (a) Type 1 and (b) Type 2 diabetes in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819267, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase access to addiction support in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819266, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to support hospices in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819265, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase levels of cleanliness in hospitals in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819264, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce A&E waiting times in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819263, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of dentist appointments in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819262, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve hospital food for patients in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819261, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of available general practice appointments in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819260, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of practising (a) dentists and (b) dental (i) hygienists, (ii) therapists and (iii) nurses.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819233, "askingMemberId": 5063, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for its policies of reports of the alleged use of Ukrainian children by Russian forces in attacks on Ukr", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819232, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many overheating incidents have been logged in NHS hospitals in the East of England in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819230, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces recruits have received a conditional offer letter within 10 days from the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force since 1 January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819229, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-09T00:00:00", "uin": "64871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2025 to Question 63159 on South Fylde Line, what discussions she has had with local (a) communities and (b) stakeholders on future service improvements on the Lytham to Preston ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819228, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-09T00:00:00", "uin": "64870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2025 to Question 63159 on South Fylde Line, what interim measures she is considering to improve capacity on the Lytham to Preston line before 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819227, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Neighbourhood Health Service on dental services in rural constituencies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819226, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Neighbourhood Health Service on healthcare in rural constituencies.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819214, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which companies have been awarded contracts for the (a) provision, (b) maintenance and (c) refurbishment of service family accommodation properties in East Wiltshire constituency; and if he will publish details o", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819213, "askingMemberId": 5198, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64866", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 26 June 2025 to Question 61659 on Research: Investment, if the Economic Secretary to the Treasury will meet with the hon. Member for Dorking and Horley to discuss research and development f", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819212, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will require local authorities to provide family hubs in communities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819211, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to develop a national outcomes framework for family hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819210, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether funding for family hubs will be included in the Child Poverty Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819208, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64862", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding was allocated to family hubs in the Spending Review 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819207, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that family hubs are available in all areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819206, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of family hubs playing on (a) neighbourhood health and (b) the delivery of integrated community-based health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819205, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that that integrated family hubs are available to support families in local communities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819204, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that schools in (a) Newcastle-under-Lyme constituency and (b) Staffordshire are able to offer high quality music education through (i) the national curriculum and (", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819203, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64857", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the (a) adequacy and (b) clarity of HM Revenue & Customs guidance for employers on workplace nursery schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819202, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support people with bladder and bowel control conditions in Devon.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819201, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage employers to adopt (a) tax-free childcare and (b) other workplace nursery schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819200, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of establishing a national glaucoma pathway, in the context of similar models in (a) Wales and (b) Scotland.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819199, "askingMemberId": 4861, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the annual administrative cost has been of providing (a) delinked payments and (b) the Basic Payment Scheme since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819195, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle (a) extremist radicalisation and (b) forms of non-ideological violence.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819194, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of a high altitude nuclear explosion on the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819193, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64850", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of a replacement to the Afghan Citizens Resettlement Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819192, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a replacement to the Afghan Relocations and Assistance Policy.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819191, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effectiveness of (a) the Get Set Progress scheme and (b) paid internship programmes for disabled people; and what discussions he has had with Cab", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819190, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support research into how neurodiverse conditions manifest in women.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819189, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the gender gap in neurodiversity diagnosis in (a) Yeovil constituency, (b) Somerset and (c) England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819188, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the (a) identification and (b) support for neurodivergent girls at school.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819187, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Act 2018, what steps his Department will take to ensure British Overseas Territories implement public registers of b", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819186, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) encourage breastfeeding and (b) support mothers who choose to breastfeed.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819185, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote digital literacy education in schools to encourage the responsible use of mobile technology.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819184, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with (a) parents, (b) students and (c) teachers on the management of mobile phone use in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819183, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64840", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of mobile phone usage in schools on (a) levels of bullying and (b) safeguarding.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819182, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support (a) teachers and (b) school leaders to enforce mobile phone usage policies in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819181, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of mobile phone use on (a) student behaviour and (b) academic performance in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819180, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of her Department's guidance on mobile phone use among young people in schools, published in February 2024, on the use of mobile phones in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819179, "askingMemberId": 4671, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has commissioned research on the use of mobile phones by young people outside of school.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819178, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64835", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 1.24 of the Review Body on Senior Salaries publication Forty-seventh annual report on senior salaries published in May 2025, what steps the Government is taking to reduce excessive (a", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819177, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64834", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance has been given to Cabinet ministers by the (a) Independent Adviser on Ministerial Standards and (b) Cabinet Office on whether Ministers who personally receive donations from trade unions (i) must a", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819176, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64833", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether appointments to the School Support Staff Negotiating Body will be included in the Public Bodies Order in Council; and whether the chair appointment will be classified as a Significant Appointment.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819175, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64832", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Conclusion of His Majesty The King\u2019s free Portrait Scheme, published on 28 November 2024, what the percentage take-up rate was for (a) UK Government depa", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819174, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64831", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54760 on Civil Servants: London, whether he plans to require any civil servants based in London to compulsorily relocate as part of the Places for Growth scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819173, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64830", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54820 on Civil Service: Equality, if he will make it his policy to (a) publish the new network guidance on gov.uk and (b) place it in the House of Commons Librar", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819172, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64829", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2025 to Question 54280 on Civil Servants: Pay, whether civil servants in her Department that are relocated outside of London will have their pay reduced; and whether civil servan", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819171, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64828", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 May 2025 to Question 53204 on Central Government: Empty Property, whether the InSite database is accessible to the public.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819170, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64827", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54822 on Cabinet Office: Directors, whether Baroness Casey will be a member of the Cabinet Office Board.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819169, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64826", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54828 on Civil Servants: Training, if he will publish the full training (a) documentation and (b) modules prepared for the course.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819168, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reserve service days were completed by the Volunteer Reserves in the last five financial years by rank.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819167, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many volunteer reservists completed (a) up to 18, (b) 19 to 26 and (c) over 27 reserve service days in the last five financial years by service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819166, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, what his target date is ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819165, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, whether nuclear certific", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819164, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the United States' decision to pause certain arms supplies to Ukraine.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819163, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his United States counterpart on that country's decision to pause certain arms supplies to Ukraine.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819162, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many volunteer reservists received an annual bounty in the last five financial years by (a) service and (b) rank.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819161, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department was of the volunteer reserve annual bounty in the last five financial years by service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819159, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department was of volunteer reserve pay excluding annual bounties in the last five financial years by service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819158, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reserve service days were completed by the Volunteer Reserves in the last five financial years by service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819157, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64815", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what approvals process is required by the Military Aviation Authority for the use of (a) reconnaissance and (b) kinetic drones on UK military bases.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819155, "askingMemberId": 5082, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the Armed Forces Covenant Duty across his Departmental responsibilities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819154, "askingMemberId": 5082, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of extending the Armed Forces Covenant Duty across her Departmental responsibilities.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819153, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many orders of electronic jamming equipment his Department has made for use by the armed forces since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819144, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to include the safety of road workers in its Road Safety strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819138, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the list of geographical areas in which her Department will encourage private landlords to house asylum seekers..", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819137, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what data his Department holds on water quality in (a) lakes and (b) rivers in Ashfield constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819136, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Bus Manufacturing Expert Panel has made an assessment of trends in the level of demand for buses; and whether they have considered the (a) location and (b) type of demand over the next 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819135, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help ensure adequate provision of apprenticeships in Ashfield constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819134, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level of preparedness in the event of a coordinated cyber-attack on public service infrastructure.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819133, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential risk of a coordinated cyber-attack on public service infrastructure.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819132, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to ensure the safety of women and girls on public transport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819131, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of reducing the bus fare cap to \u00a32.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819130, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64802", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) effectiveness and (b) availability of Government support for small businesses in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819129, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64801", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Windsor Framework on SMEs in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819128, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the review by the Minister for Social Security and Disability on PIP eligibility will incorporate (a) regional data and (b) stakeholder views from (i) Northern Ireland and (ii) Upper?Bann constituen", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819127, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether (a) Universal Credit and (b) PIP awards in Northern Ireland will remain indexed to inflation until 2029-30 under proposed welfare reforms.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819126, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of proposed reforms to (a) PIP and (b) Universal Credit on (i) community cohesion and (ii) equitable access to benefits in Northern Irelan", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819125, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of freezing the health element of Universal Credit for new claimants from April?2026 on (a) poverty rates, (b) the cost of living and (c) workforce p", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819124, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-09T00:00:00", "uin": "64796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) operational cost and (b) salary of the Chief Executive of the Office of Road and Rail is; what assessment she has made of the (i) value for money and (ii) effectiveness of that office; and whether ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819123, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 63169 on MBR Acres, what support his Department is providing to MBR.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819122, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will allow exhibition poultry from Northern Ireland to return from short-term events in Great Britain under general licence subject to veterinary certification.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819121, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to provide financial assistance to hobbyist poultry breeders in Northern Ireland to meet veterinary certification costs for participation in shows in Great Britain.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819120, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to introduce a movement protocol for non-commercial avian species used for (a) shows and (b) exhibitions.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819119, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the risk of exhibition poultry returning from short-term events in Great Britain to Northern Ireland; and whether he plans to introduce (a) veterin", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819118, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64790", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Department of Agriculture, Environment and Rural Affairs in Northern Ireland and (b) Animal and Plant Health Agency on creating an (i) a", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819117, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64789", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the potential impact of the (a) testing and (b) certification requirements for poultry under the Windsor Framework on non-commercial exhib", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819116, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of reinstating the general licence conditions for the movement of exhibition poultry between Northern Ireland and Grea", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819113, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, when he plans to publish a consultation on the regulation of frontier AI systems.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819112, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will provide assurances that there will be no further delays by (a) Anguilla, (b) Bermuda, (c) the British Virgin Islands and (d) Turks and Caicos Islands to implement ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819111, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his Department\u2019s policies of maintaining the BN(O) visa scheme with a five-year pathway to indefinite leave to r", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819110, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64784", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the safe return of British nationals from countries impacted by airspace closures in the Middle East.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819152, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many orders of electronic surveillance equipment his Department has made for use by the armed forces since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819151, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many orders of electronic warfare equipment has his Department made for use by the armed forces since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819150, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the electronic warfare equipment used by the armed forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819149, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the quality of electronic warfare equipment used by the armed forces in training exercises.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819148, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to provide electronic warfare equipment to the army for use in training exercises.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819251, "askingMemberId": 4480, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Food and Drink Sector Council last met; and when they plan to meet next.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819238, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64777", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 April 2025 to Question 43478 on Admiralty House, if he will make it his policy to rent out the two empty flats in Admiralty House at a market rate.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819237, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64776", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department has issued on who should pay for the cost of (a) water and (b) electricity used in official residences occupied by Ministers.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819225, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make it her policy to lay a Legislative Reform Order to permit outdoor religious weddings.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819224, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the (a) applicants and (b) Community Law Partnership received legal aid in relation to the case that resulted in the High Court decision of [2024] EWHC 1137 (Admin).", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819223, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether (a) she and (b) her Ministers have had discussions with (i) the Chair and (ii) members of the Working Group on Anti-Muslim Hatred/Islamophobia to discuss its work.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819222, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64772", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, what plans he has to appoint an Envoy for the Nations and Regions.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819221, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Welsh Government on their Collections Blueprint 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819220, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department has provided to public authorities on what are reasonable charges under the Environmental Information Regulations regime.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819219, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2025 to Question 61181,on Coastal Erosion: Flood Control, how much capital funding for flood defence his Department has allocated for each year of the", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819218, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of seasonal water tariffs on households with gardens.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819217, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2025 to Question 57663, on Water Charges: Social Tariffs, how social tariffs will be funded; and what assessment he has made of the potential impact o", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819216, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2025 to Question 61181 on Coastal Erosion: Flood Control, whether the quantum of the \u00a32.65 billion funding over 2024-25 and 2025-26 has been amended s", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819215, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64765", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, whether the Law Officers have met with (a) Dominic Grieve and (b) the members of the Working Group on Anti-Muslim Hatred/Islamophobia to discuss the working group and the definition of Islamophobia.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819147, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she is considering providing metro mayors with powers to levy tourist taxes in their areas.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819146, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations she has received from the Mayor of London on a tourist tax for London.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819312, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the current tariff for the Minor Surgery Directed Enhanced Service in the context of rising operational costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819299, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment has she made of the potential impact of the closure of the FA Futsal Committee on futsal governance in England; and if she will publish a long-term development strategy for the sp", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819283, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to extend the requirement for mandatory anti-lock braking systems to include all new 125cc motorcycles.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819231, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether funding will be made available to devolved Governments under the Barnett formula from the NHS England Ten Year Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819259, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2025 to Question 60503 on Housing: Construction, what steps her Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) prevent future cost pressures on mat", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819258, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64757", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of households relying on high-cost credit to meet living expenses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819257, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64756", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of average savings held by (a) low-income households and (b) pensioners for meeting emergency or unforeseen costs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819256, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64755", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to incentivise saving.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819255, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64754", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to reduce the burden of (a) food costs, (b) energy bills and (c) credit costs on households.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819254, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64753", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has she made of the potential impact of food price and energy inflation on (a) low-income households, (b) pensioners and (c) disabled people.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819253, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the proportion of overall household spending by lower income households on energy costs.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819252, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what contribution GB Energy has made to reducing (a) gas, (b) electricity and (c) fuel bills since its establishment in May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819250, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support British farmers producing (a) cereal, (b) milk, (c) butter, (d) beef and (e) other staple food items.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819249, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the reduction in ODA on his Department\u2019s work on human rights.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819248, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what the (a) annual spending allocation profile and (b) planned timeline is for the \u00a31.25 funding pledge to Gavi.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819247, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what proportion of the UK's pledge at the Gavi summit on 25 June 2025 will be delivered through the International Finance Facility for Immunisation.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819246, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2025 to Question 59861 on Development Aid, which multilateral organisations he will prioritise funding.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819245, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2025 to Question 59861 on Development Aid, what reforms he plans to drive in the multilateral system, whether he plans to do this in concert", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819244, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64744", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what dates have been set for (a) the inaugural meeting and (b) any future meetings of the London Coalition on Sustainable Sovereign Debt.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819243, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64743", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what budget has been allocated for the London Coalition on Sustainable Sovereign Debt.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819242, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to the Taliban on the treatment of (a) LGBT+ people, (b) women and girls and (c) people from ethnic Hazara communities.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819241, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the UN Human Rights Council 59: UK Statement on the report of the Special Rapporteur on Afghanistan, published on 16 June 2025, what steps he is taking to s", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819240, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Women, Peace and Security National Action Plan, report to Parliament 2024 to 2025, published on 17 June 2025, what support the UK is giving to a \u2018Specia", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819239, "askingMemberId": 4358, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Women, Peace and Security National Action Plan, report to Parliament 2024 to 2025, published on 17 June 2025, what representations were made to the Spec", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819145, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department shares information with local police forces on the criminal records of asylum seekers placed in their area.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819143, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people claiming asylum had a criminal record before entering the UK in the most recent period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819142, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ascertain previous offences of people claiming asylum in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819141, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of asylum seekers have had their DNA taken on arrival in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819308, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether the earlier draft of the UK-Mauritius Treaty from October 2024 gave the UK a unilateral right to extend the lease after the initial 99 year period.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819307, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to his Oral Statement of 7 October 2024 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Negotiations, Official Report, column 46, on what evidential basis he stated that th", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819306, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what payments to Mauritius under the UK-Mauritius Treaty will be included in the UK\u2019s calculation of the (a) 3.5% core defence spending and (b) defence-related investments.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819305, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to his Oral Statement of 7 October 2024 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Negotiations, Official Report, column 46, on what evidential basis he stated that Ma", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819304, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to Article 6 of the UK-Mauritius Treaty, what discussions he has had with his Mauritian counterpart on (a) visits to and (b) resettlement of the Chagos Archipe", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819303, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 62581 on Chagos Islands: Sovereignty, whether his Department has made an estimate of the (a) yearly payment schedules for th", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819302, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 62580 on Chagos Islands: Sovereignty, whether he has budgeted for the first payment to Mauritius to be in financial year 202", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819300, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to his speech at the British Chambers of Commerce on 20 March 2025, how many diplomats have been seconded to businesses since 20 March 2025; what the (a) cost ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819298, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 62574 on Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Cost Effectiveness, what savings he expects to make from the FCDO2030", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819297, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 62574 on Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Cost Effectiveness, whether the FCDO2030 change programme has (a) key", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819296, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent progress has been made by the Coalition of the Willing on Ukraine.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819236, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the (a) number of students who graduated in nursing and (b) number and proportion of those graduates who were employed within six months in the last four ye", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819235, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of hospital Safer Staffing requirements on the newly qualified nurses\u2019 ability to become employed in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819234, "askingMemberId": 3952, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many newly qualified nurses have been recruited to each NHS Trust in the last four years; and how many have been recruited from overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819198, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to encourage the use of a standardised puppy contract scheme, in the context of the one promoted by The Kennel Club.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819197, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has considered developing a national mentoring scheme pairing experienced dog breeders with first-time breeders to help promote (a) high welfare and (b) informed", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819196, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has considered reforming the Licensing of Activities Involving Animals Regulations 2018 to introduce a tiered system that distinguishes between (a) low and (b) h", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819156, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications have been rejected on the grounds of dual nationality in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819140, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support the introduction of more vocational education pathways for students in Lincolnshire.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819139, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help improve access to sport for (a) children and (b) young people from disadvantaged backgrounds in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1819115, "askingMemberId": 55, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will add irreplaceable meadows to the list of irreplaceable habitats.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1819115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818997, "askingMemberId": 5274, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the UK's 41st place in the Hologic Global Women\u2019s Health Index, what steps his Department is taking to improve women's health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818996, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how his Department\u2019s 10 Year Health Plan will support patients with multiple sclerosis in receiving adequate (a) care and (b) support.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818995, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of changes to the (a) structure and (b) responsibilities of Integrated Care Boards on the (i) commissioning and (ii) delivery of mult", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818994, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the NHS England Getting It Right First Time neurology programme on the (a) quality and (b) consistency of multiple sclerosis care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818993, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish an equalities impact assessment of the proposed Personal Independence Payment reforms with specific reference to people with progressive neurological conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818992, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of proposed welfare reforms on people with (a) multiple sclerosis and (b) other fluctuating conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818991, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she has taken with Cabinet colleagues to help ensure that people with multiple sclerosis are supported to remain in employment through (a) flexible working arrangements and (b) effective symp", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818990, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking through the Get Britain Working White Paper to support people with multiple sclerosis (a) into and (b) to stay in work.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818989, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made with Cabinet colleagues of the effectiveness of the right to be forgotten in the Data Protection Act 2018, in the context of people acquitted of crimes.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818983, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department has provided to help people with arthritis to (a) remain in and (b) return to work.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818982, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of Personal Independence Payment claimants with a primary condition of arthritis.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818978, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to assess the adequacy of the clarity of the application process for the Social Fund Funeral Expenses Payment for bereaved applicants.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818977, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64701", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment she has made of the total effective tax payable by (a) the hospitality sector and (b) other sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818976, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64700", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the standard 20% VAT rate on the international competitiveness of the (a) tourism and (b) hospitality sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818975, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64699", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish a distributional impact assessment of changes to national insurance contributions on (a) low and (b) middle income workers in the hospitality industry.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818974, "askingMemberId": 5255, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64698", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the impact of changes to the employer National Insurance contributions on employment levels in the hospitality sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818973, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of reforming the eligibility criteria for the Social Fund Funeral Expenses Payment in line with the Scottish Government\u2019s Funeral Su", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818971, "askingMemberId": 5357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of simplifying the eligibility criteria for the Funeral Expenses Payment on (a) application processing times and (b) the administrat", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818969, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to integrate (a) movement and (b) exercise into cancer rehabilitation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818968, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase access to nature for young people.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818967, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking with local authorities in Leeds to support research and development across the region.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818966, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help improve rail (a) reliability and (b) performance to ensure people are able to access (i) work and (ii) educational opportunities.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818965, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, following the recent appointment of a Small Business Commissioner, what further steps he is taking to help ensure SMEs can access support.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818964, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to create high quality new developments which (a) enhance communities and (b) restore nature.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818963, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Institute for Fiscal Studies report entitled, The short- and medium-term effects of Sure Start on children\u2019s outcomes, published in May 2025, what assessment has she made of the potential ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818962, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64688", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Institute for Fiscal Studies report entitled, The short- and medium-term effects of Sure Start on children\u2019s outcomes, published in May 2025, what assessment she has made of the impact of Sure ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818961, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of Sure Start children's centres on the proportion of children receiving SEND support from an early age.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818960, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the Institute for Fiscal Studies' report entitled The short- and medium-term effects of Sure Start on children\u2019s outcomes, ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818959, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the Institute for Fiscal Studies' report entitled The short- and medium-term effects of Sure Start on children\u2019s outcom", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818958, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the report by the Institute for Fiscal Studies entitled The short- and medium-term effects of Sure Start on children\u2019s outcomes, pu", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818957, "askingMemberId": 5319, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department allocated for cadet services in (a) each of the last three financial years, (b) the 2025-26 financial year and (c) the 2026-27 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818956, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of NHS England\u2019s decision not to commission abiraterone acetate plus prednisone/prednisolone for men with high risk non metastatic prostate cance", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818955, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the randomised control trial study report entitled Cost utility analysis of adding abiraterone acetate plus prednisone/prednisolone to long term hormone therapy in newly diagnosed", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818954, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of requiring state schools to engage with music hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818953, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the assessment of the Music Hub programme by the National Centre for Social Research will report on the progression of students.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818952, "askingMemberId": 5286, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the capital grant for musical instruments has been distributed in (a) total and (b) each region of England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818951, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64677", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2025 to Question 63473 on Origin Marking: Occupied Territories, how many compliance checks HMRC undertook to identify whether goods labelled as originating from Israel were produced ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818950, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her plans are for the asylum seekers housed in hotels, in the context of the Chancellor\u2019s recent pledge to end all hotel accommodation for asylum seekers by 2029.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818949, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what role Natural England will play under the Planning and Infrastructure Bill in ensuring improvements to nature are delivered; and what statutory powers and funding will be gra", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818948, "askingMemberId": 5353, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Planning and Infrastructure Bill on the (a) duties and (b) targets set in the Environment Act 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818947, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818946, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818945, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818944, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818943, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818942, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818941, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818940, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information her Department holds on the dates on which the leases for West Midlands Trains' rolling stock expire; and which entity owns those trains.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818939, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64665", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818938, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818937, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818936, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818935, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818934, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818933, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818932, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818931, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818930, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818929, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to help improve recruitment and retention in the Armed Forces.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818928, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential role of family hubs in (a) neighbourhood health and (a) the delivery of integrated community-based health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818927, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many claims have been (a) made to and (b) rejected by the compensation schemes for sub-postmasters impacted by Horizon IT; and what proportion of those claims have successfully concluded.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818926, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) guidance and (b) training is provided to (i) teachers and (ii) school staff to help ensure they are (A) confident and (B) equipped to (1) educate pupils about online grooming and (2) respond appropriat", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818925, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve online safety education in schools to help children (a) recognise and (b) respond to online grooming.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818924, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking is taking to ensure that people diagnosed with invasive lobular breast cancer are routinely offered MRI scans for follow-up monitoring.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818923, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prioritise UK-trained resident doctors in the allocation of specialist training posts; and what steps he is taking to increase the number of such funded posts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818922, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the scope of the Government\u2019s independent commission into adult social care include the means testing which underpins the Disabled Facilities Grant.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818921, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has had discussions with the Authority administering the Infected Blood Compensation Scheme on (a) the number of claims made, (b) the number rejected and (c) the proportion of claimants ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818920, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many claims have been made to the LGBT Financial Recognition Scheme; and what steps he is taking to ensure all potential recipients are aware of the scheme before it closes in December 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818919, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many claims have been (a) made to and (b) rejected by the LGBT Financial Recognition Scheme; and what proportion of those claims have successfully concluded.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818918, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS podiatry services in Mid Sussex constituency are adequately resourced.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818917, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of podiatrists; and if he will (a) reinstate full student bursaries and (b) introduce incentives to encourage recruitment and retention in", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818916, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of hours spent by (a) his Department and (b) Baroness Casey\u2019s review team on the review since (a) 5 July 2024 and (b) 3 January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818915, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Windrush Compensation Scheme will (a) deal with outstanding claims and (b) be closed.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818914, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people are in Baroness Casey\u2019s review team.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818913, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64639", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many meetings officials in his Department have had with (a) Baroness Casey and (b) her team (i) before and (ii) after 2 January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818912, "askingMemberId": 5283, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64638", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times he has met Baroness Casey since (a) 5 July 2024 and (b) 3 January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818911, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what resources her Department provides to employers to help them meet compliance obligations during each stage of the Employment Rights Bill roadmap\u2019s implementation.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818910, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what criteria will be used to evaluate the phased implementation approach outlined in the Employment Rights Bill roadmap.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818909, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether the Employment Rights Bill roadmap includes contingency measures if key stakeholders report insufficient capacity to meet implementation requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818908, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64634", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the measures scheduled for implementation in the Employment Rights Bill on businesses in (a) 2026 and (b) 2027.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818907, "askingMemberId": 5203, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what discussions she has had with business representatives on the feasibility of the commencement dates set out in the Employment Rights Bill implementation roadmap.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818906, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claims for compensation her Department has received for the Windrush Compensation Scheme since that scheme began; and how many and what proportion of those claims were (a) rejected and (b) su", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818905, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64631", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has considered making relationships, sex and health education mandatory in (a) sixth form colleges and (b) other further education institutions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818904, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of extending existing provisions for mandatory Relationships, Sex and Health Education under the Children and Social Work Act 2017 to ensure everyone u", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818903, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64629", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the reduction of face to face banking options for all customers who find digital and telephone banking difficult to access.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818902, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64628", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support Surrey County Council to improve support for children who go missing or are at risk of exploitation.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818901, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support Surrey County Council to deliver more housing for care leavers to improve Education, Employment and Training opportunities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818900, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support Surrey County Council improve collaborative safety planning.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818899, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of time required to ensure adequate levels of (a) awareness and (b) voter registration ahead of a General Election in which 16 year olds vote.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818898, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of replacing the role of local authorities with committees in planning decision on local representation in those d", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818897, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of Carer\u2019s Allowance overpayments on individuals in receipt of the benefit; and what steps her Department is taking to support carers in r", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818896, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Minister for Rail's letter to the hon. Member for Weald of Kent on rail, dated 14 April 2025, which hon. Members were invited to meet with the Minister for Rail to discuss the Kent and Med", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818895, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Minister for Rail's letter to the hon. Member for Weald of Kent on rail, dated 14 April 2025, on what basis the Minister for Rail selected attendees for the recent meeting between hon. Mem", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818894, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Minister for Rail's letter to the hon. Member for Weald of Kent on rail, dated 14 April 2025, whether (a) the Minister for Rail and (b) officials in her Department had met with the Kent an", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818893, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultation her Department has undertaken with UK-based bus manufacturers on the potential impact of Section 37 of the Bus Services (No. 2) Bill [Lords] on future sales of (a) hydrogen-fuel cell and (b) h", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818892, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when he received the report from the Independent Monitoring Panel relating to the operation of the UK internal market; and when he plans to publish it.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818891, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64617", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when he received the Independent Review of the Windsor Framework; and when he plans to publish it.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818890, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the uplift to the basic standard allowance of Universal Credit on the incomes of low income households in Bournemouth East constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818889, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of mobile phone signal in Chichester constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818888, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact that the Principles of Process Safety Leadership for the offshore UK Continental Shelf energy industry agreed between the Health and Safety Ex", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818887, "askingMemberId": 5196, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which oil and gas (a) duty holders and (b) installations on the UK Continental Shelf were subject to enforcement action by the Health and Safety Executive in relation to the management of safety critica", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818886, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on proposals for a Dorset Clean Energy Supercluster.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818885, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential suitability of locations in Dorset for a new Small Modular Nuclear Reactor.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818884, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase retention rates for domestically trained NHS (a) doctors and (b) other clinical staff.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818883, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment has she made of the potential impact of the Social and Affordable Homes Programme on housing affordability in Bournemouth.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818882, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the 10 year Social and Affordable Housing Programme. how many new council homes will be built in (a) Bournemouth and (b) Dorset.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818881, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many new social homes will be delivered in Bournemouth as a result of the 10 year Social and Affordable Homes Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818880, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64606", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of job opportunities for newly qualified nurses.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818879, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the implementation of the Cass Review on trans people under the age of 18.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818878, "askingMemberId": 5175, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many football bans have been given to offenders in the last (a) 12 and (b) 18 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818877, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the level of risk of eviction of social housing tenants who remain in a property after a joint tenant has served notice to quit (a) in cases invol", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818876, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to review the legal duty of care between universities and Students' Unions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818875, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of risk assessments for Students' Union activities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818874, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2025 to Question 61101 on Darwin Plus: Finance, when he plans to announce the amount of future funding for Darwin Plus.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818873, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2025 to Question 61101 on Darwin Plus: Finance, how many years the funding commitment is for.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818872, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of protecting funding for the Darwin Plus scheme beyond 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818871, "askingMemberId": 5167, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to accelerate grid connection times for small and medium-sized enterprises and manufacturers participating in grid-balancing schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818870, "askingMemberId": 5251, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make a comparative assessment of the number of appeals permitted by the (a) Independent Appeals Service, (b) British Parking Association Independent Appeals Service a", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818988, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of levels of funding for the (a) Medical Research Council and (b) National Institute for Health and Care Research.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818987, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with (a) the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency and (b) the National institute for Health and Care Excellence on access to innovative treatment for pati", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818986, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the national cancer plan will consider (a) astrocytoma and (b) other types of brain tumours.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818985, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the amount of funding available for research into (a) low grade glioma and (b) astrocytoma.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818984, "askingMemberId": 4872, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help increase levels of life expectancy for people with (a) low grade glioma and (b) astrocytoma.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818981, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department has allocated to (a) the Red Arrows and (b) other military display teams in the Spending Review 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818980, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help protect places of worship in Greater Manchester.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818979, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to replace the Hawk T1 fleet used by the Red Arrows.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818972, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2025 to Question 42299 on Defence Growth Board, whether the Defence Growth Board has met since 3 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818970, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support (a) dyscalculic learners and(b) learners with maths learning difficulties.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818861, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64585", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to provide provide financial support for communities seeking to bring disused pubs back into use.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818860, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64584", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders are currently released on license.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818859, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64583", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an estimate of the potential impact of reducing GREAT campaign funding on economic growth.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818858, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64582", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the year-on-year spending associated with the Chagos Islands deal will be funded.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818857, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64581", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of UK hospitality's press release entitled, One third of hospitality businesses now operating at a loss, published 2 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818856, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish the New Towns Taskforce recommendations before 23 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818853, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of reservists received a tax free bounty in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818848, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64578", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) service and (b) service family accommodation properties there are in East Wiltshire, by property type.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818847, "askingMemberId": 4858, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many homes his Department owns in East Wiltshire constituency; and how many of those (a) have Ministry of Defence tenants, (b) have private tenants and (c) are vacant.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818845, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64576", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the business rates system on pub closures.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818844, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64575", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the eligibility criteria for the Help to Save scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818843, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an estimate of the amount of capital funding that public sector bodies will spend on (a) building and (b) purchasing houses between July 2024 and July 2029.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818842, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the document entitled Economic appraisal for investing in local highways maintenance, published on 26 September 2024, what progress her Department has made on publishing its response to the re", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818841, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of the Annual Local Authority Road Maintenance Survey Report 2025, published on 18 March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818840, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64571", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse for Senior Civil Service pay in the (a) 2024-25 and (b) 2025-26 financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818839, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether board appointments to the National Data Library will be included in the Public Appointments Order in Council; and whether the chair for the National Data Library will be classif", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818838, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64569", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 May 2025 to Question 49382 on 9 Downing Street: Repairs and Maintenance, whether the relevant narrative entry in the transparency data will show which OCS invoice relates to the refu", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818837, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64568", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2025 to Question 53901 on Data, Statistics and Research on Sex and Gender Independent Review, how the UK Statistics Authority plans to inform (a) Parliament and (b) the public of", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818836, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2025 to Question 54274 on Government Departments: Publicity, if he will publish the spending control business case and approval for the 2025 National Minimum Wage and N", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818835, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64566", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54781 on Arm\u2019s Length Bodies: Equality, whether there is any monitoring of the EDI spending exemptions authorised by Arm\u2019s Length Bodies; and whether there is an", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818834, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64565", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2025 to Question 57737 on European Parliament Members: Workplace Pensions, which public body holds information on the pension scheme liabilities for UK MEPs from 2009 up to the ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818833, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64564", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54800 on Government Departments: Press Offices, if he will publish the guidance on the use of party political commodities at Government press conferences.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818831, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64563", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54812 on Government Departments: media, what guidance is issued by the Government Communication Service on the procurement of external public relations companies", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818830, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64562", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54825 on Government Departments: Training, if he will publish the updated guidance on the use of external venues.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818829, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64561", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54812 on Government Departments: media, if he will list the 180 companies that expressed an interest in providing external public relations under the RM6364 Medi", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818828, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64560", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the entry in his Department's publication entitled Cabinet Office Commercial Pipeline 2024-26, of 31 October 2024 P2465: CO COMMERCIAL: Venue Booking Services, who the supplier is of those serv", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818827, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64559", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the response to the Freedom of Information Act request reference FOI2025/05753 of 12 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818826, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64558", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2025 to Question 59366 on Cabinet Office: staff, whether his Department has a target for (a) voluntary and (b) compulsory exits; and what communications have been sent to civil ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818826", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818825, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what incentives he is providing for (a) Anguilla, (b) Bermuda, (c) the British Virgin Islands and (d) the Turks and Caicos Islands to make swifter progress at delivering Legi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818825", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818824, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64556", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how he will assess compliance with commitments made at the 2024 Joint Ministerial Council by (a) Anguilla, (b) Bermuda, (c) the British Virgin Islands, (d) the Cayman Islands", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818824", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818823, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64555", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding was (a) allocated and (b) spent on railways in Wales between 2010 and 2024 by fiscal period.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818823", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818822, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what progress (a) Anguilla, (b) Bermuda, (c) the British Virgin Islands, (d) the Cayman Islands and (e) the Turks and Caicos Islands have made on implementing Legitimate Inte", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818822", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818821, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that public services do not use non-disclosure agreements on whistleblowers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818821", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818820, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64552", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many small and medium-sized enterprises in Northern Ireland have used the Trader Support Service; and what proportion of the service\u2019s costs have supported those businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818820", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818814, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64551", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has allocated funding to continue the Trader Support Service beyond 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818814", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818813, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64550", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the Trader Support Service\u2019s costs are spent on (a) administrative and (b) operational overheads.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818813", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818812, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64549", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the value for money of the Trader Support Service for business support outcomes in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818812", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818811, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64548", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total cost to the public purse is for the Trader Support Service since 11 June 2020, broken down by financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818811", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818808, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that the recommendations of the Motor Insurance Taskforce are implemented equitably in all regions; and how she plans to monitor this.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818808", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818807, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Motor Insurance Taskforce (a) has analysed and (b) will publish regional insurance pricing data.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818807", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818806, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her planned timetable is for the publication of the Motor Insurance Taskforce's final report; and whether it will include regional breakdowns of findings and recommendations.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818806", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818805, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which (a) consumer representatives and (b) regional insurers in Northern Ireland have been consulted by the Motor Insurance Taskforce.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818805", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818804, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Motor Insurance Taskforce has considered the motor insurance market in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818804", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818803, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when decisions on applications for (a) leave in line and (b) status in line will resume.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818803", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818801, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of proposed reductions to Official Development Assistance on women and girls\u2019 reproductive (a) health and (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818801", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818800, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, when his Depa", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818800", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818799, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, when his Depa", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818799", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818798, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, what the tota", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818798", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818796, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2025 to Question 57348 on Universities: Freedom of Expression, what steps she plans to take in response to breaches of those regulations.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818796", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818795, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2025 to Question 57348 on Universities: Freedom of Expression, what steps she has taken to ensure enforcement of those regulations.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818795", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818788, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64534", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818787, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64533", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how many staff in her Department have permission to work remotely outside the UK; and in which countries those staff are based.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818784, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to recognise overseas professional qualifications held by British National (Overseas) migrants.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818783, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of British National (Overseas) visa holder dependent school pupils who are excluded from home fee status.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818782, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has considered granting British National (Overseas) visa holders parity with EU nationals who retain a five-year route to settled status under the UK-EU Withdrawal Agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818781, "askingMemberId": 5046, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help improve (a) safety and (b) regulation in the non-surgical cosmetics sector.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818776, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2025 to 60968 on Insomnia: Lancashire, what steps his Department is taking to promote awareness of self-referral options to NHS talking therapies for people with i", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818775, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2025 to Question 60968 on Insomnia: Lancashire, what data his Department holds on the number of people who accessed NHS Talking Therapies in relation to chronic in", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818774, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2025 to Question 60968 on Insomnia: Lancashire, whether his Department has had discussions with Lancashire and South Cumbria Integrated Care Board on its insomnia ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818773, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64525", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an estimate of the revenue to the public purse from the taxes paid by British National (Overseas) visa holders since 2021.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818772, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the potential impact of extending the qualifying period for indefinite leave to remain for British National (Overseas) visa holders on the number of young people who (a) hold those", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818771, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's planned timetable is for issuing guidance to dependents of BN(O) visa holders who plan to start university in 2026 on whether they will be eligible for home fee status.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818766, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, what assessment he has m", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818765, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, what proportion of time ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818764, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, whether he consulted the", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818763, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the press release entitled UK to purchase F-35As and join NATO mission as Government steps up national security and delivers defence dividend, published on 24 June 2025, what the in service date", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818762, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the Defence Housing Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818761, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many drones have been purchased by the British army for use in sport since 5 July 2024, by unit.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818760, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for each British Army Unit holding stocks of electronic counter measure kits, what the (a) in service and (b) out of service dates are in each case.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818759, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64515", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how may electronic counter measure kits are in use by the British army; and if he will publish a list of  units in which they are used.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818758, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64514", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to accelerate approvals by the Military Aviation Authority for the use of (a) reconnaissance and (b) kinetic drones on UK military bases.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818757, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure the British army is able to train in trench warfare conditions across the defence estate.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818755, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64512", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission has issued guidance on members\u2019 associations set up as limited companies (a) registering with the C", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818754, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54870 on Parking: Fines, if she will publish the research provided by the (a) Parking and Traffic Regulations Outside London, (b) British Parking Association an", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818753, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64510", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 56829 on Speed Limits, whether her Department has plans to update 20mph zone guidance for England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818752, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64509", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what her Department's policy position is on 15 minute cities.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818750, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an estimate of the proportion of UK pension scheme assets invested in fossil fuel-related holdings; and what plans she has to (a) encourage phased divestment from fossil ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818748, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64507", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what private businesses she has consulted on the business rates system.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818745, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether the parental leave review will examine options for reducing administrative burdens on employers in managing statutory parental leave and pay.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818744, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of proposed changes to parental leave entitlements on small and medium-sized enterprises, as part of the ongoing review.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818743, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has had discussions with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the ONS's classification of British Steel as part of the public non-financial corporations subsector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818741, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the lifespan of the blast furnaces at British Steel in Scunthorpe.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818736, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has had discussions with Oxfordshire County Council on its planned introduction of traffic filters by Oxford in 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818735, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 62275 on Defence: Finance, when the amount of his Department's contribution will be (a) determined and (b) published.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818734, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64500", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June to Question 62275 on Defence: Finance, whether the FCDO contribution referred to will be included in the Defence budget in 2028.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818733, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64499", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 62275 on Defence: Finance, whether the his Department's contribution will be included in the defence budget after 2027.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818732, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with local authorities on the use of fixed-penalty notices for households for minor waste receptacle issues.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818730, "askingMemberId": 5046, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to introduce a national screening programme for prostate cancer; and what steps his Department is taking to improve outcomes for people affected by the disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818724, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64496", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Environment Agency has spent delivering biodiversity net gain (a) above and (b) below mean high water on projects related to flood defence in the latest period for which d", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818723, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Environment Agency has spent on (a) mitigation and (b) compensation for flood defence projects in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818722, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of hours the Environment Agency has spent providing advice to the Marine Management Organisation on marine licence applications in e", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818721, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of hours Natural England has spent providing advice to the Marine Management Organisation on marine licence applications in each of ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818720, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many hours the Marine Management Organisation has spent determining (a) Band 2 and (b) Band 3 marine licence applications in each of the last five years for which data is available", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818719, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many marine licenses were determined by the Marine Management Organisation for (a) removal of abandoned vessels, (b) firework displays, (c) maintenance of bridges or cantilevered s", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818718, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much income the Marine Management Organisation have received from charges for (a) harbour revision orders and (b) harbour empowerment order applications in each of the last five ye", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818717, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many hours the Marine Management Organisation have spent processing (a) harbour revision orders and (b) harbour empowerment orders in each of the last five years for which data is ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818716, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2025 to Question 62692 on Air Ambulance Services: Contracts, if he will take steps to establish which air ambulance organisations hold contracts with NHS organisat", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818715, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing mandatory prison sentences for people operating unregulated care homes for children.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818714, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to appoint an independent ombudsman to provide oversight of the Independent Custody Visiting Association.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818713, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to increase its oversight of the Independent Custody Visiting Association.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818712, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of undertaking a review into the operations of the Independent Custody Visiting Association (a) in Hampshire and (b) nationally.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818711, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to make amendments to existing legislation on the operation of the Independent Custody Visiting Association.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818710, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the operations of the Independent Custody Visiting Association.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818709, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to take steps to ensure guidance is followed on the operations of the Independent Custody Visiting Association.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818708, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64480", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure (a) structured training programmes and (b) required materials are provided to new volunteers in the Independent Custody Visiting Association.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818707, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64479", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure (a) guidance and (b) standards are followed on the operation of the Independent Custody Visiting Association.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818706, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 March 2025 to Question 39917 on Unmanned Air Systems: Procurement, how many military drones in (a) logistics, (b) strike and (c) intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance roles we", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818705, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Minister for Migration and Citizenship plans to respond to the correspondence of 2 May 2025 from the hon. Member for Hazel Grove, Ref LS06151.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818702, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the Child Maintenance Service\u2019s approach to domestic abuse on the Government\u2019s mission to halve violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818701, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government\u2019s response to the consultation entitled Child Maintenance: Improving the Collection and Transfer of Payments, published on 23 June 2025, what the eligibility criteria wi", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818700, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government\u2019s response to the consultation entitled Child Maintenance: Improving the Collection and Transfer of Payments, published on 23 June 2025, whether she has made an assessme", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818699, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government\u2019s response to the consultation entitled Child Maintenance: Improving the Collection and Transfer of Payments, published on 23 June 2025, what steps she plans to take to ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818698, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government\u2019s response to the consultation entitled Child Maintenance: Improving the Collection and Transfer of Payments, published on 23 June 2025, what steps she plans to take to ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818697, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government\u2019s response to the consultation entitled Child Maintenance: Improving the Collection and Transfer of Payments, published on 23 June 2025, what steps she is taking to prev", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818696, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government\u2019s response to the consultation entitled Child Maintenance: Improving the Collection and Transfer of Payments, published on 23 June 2025, what steps she is taking to impr", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818695, "askingMemberId": 4673, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to introduce legislation to implement the Government\u2019s response to the consultation entitled Child Maintenance: Improving the Collection and Transfer of Payments, published on 23 June 202", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818694, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to her Department's press release entitled New dawn for rail as South Western services return to public hands, published on 25 May 2025, what her plans are for operators who fail to meet the stan", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818693, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64467", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what process her Department took to appoint Chiltern Railways as the operator of East-West Rail from Oxford-Milton Keynes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818692, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64466", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will publish any assessment that National Highways have made of the flooding of the A421 at Marston Moreteyne in September 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818691, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding her Department has allocated to reducing the number of rail replacement services required on Thameslink services in the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818690, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the press release entitled Government pledges greater growth for the coach sector ahead of National Coach Week, published on 6 May 2025, whether she plans to take steps to support the coach se", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818689, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to her Department's guidance entitled Persons with Reduced Mobility National Technical Specification Notice, published in December 2017, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of Appendix", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818688, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64462", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, if she will make an estimate of the number of Government announcements which were made in the House of Commons prior to a Ministerial announcement in the media since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818687, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64461", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring landlords to update Efficiency Performance Certificates regularly.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818686, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64460", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 56032 on Housing: Costs, what steps she plans to take to incentivise developers to build at a level that reduces house prices.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818685, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64459", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department\u2019s proposed New Towns will be able to demolish areas of existing housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818684, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the impact assessment on the Universal Credit and Personal Independent Payment Bill, published on 30 June 2025, how many of those moved into relative or absolute poverty are due solely", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818682, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64457", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of Google's compliance with the AI safety commitments made at the Seoul AI Safety Summit in May 2024 in relation to its Gemini 2.5 Pro model.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818681, "askingMemberId": 4573, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64456", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to help ensure all signatory companies from the Seoul AI Safety Summit honour their commitments made at that summit.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818731, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64455", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 57278 on Water Charges, if he will make it his policy to prevent water companies from using (a) rising block tariffs and progressive a", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818729, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64454", "questionText": "To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to establish an Office of the Deputy Prime Minister.", "answeringBodyId": 23, "answeringBodyName": "Prime Minister", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818679, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64453", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 May 2025 to Question 55440 on National Landscapes, for what reason work has stopped on the (a) Cheshire Sandstone Ridge and (b) Chiltern National Landscape", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818676, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64452", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether water companies are permitted to fund social tariffs by passing costs to other residential customers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818675, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64451", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission has issued guidance on (a) companies and (b) unincorporated associations raising funds from foreign", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818674, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64450", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2025 to Question 56565 on Political Parties: Crypocurrencies, if he will publish the guidance on n", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818673, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64449", "questionText": "To ask the Right hon. Member for Kenilworth and Southam, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the value is of the (a) RDEL and (b) CDEL settlement for the Electoral Commission in each year of the Spending Review 2025; and", "answeringBodyId": 36, "answeringBodyName": "Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818780, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Universal Credit and Personal Independence Payments Bill on the Scottish Government's block grant.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818779, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64447", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the potential impact of a reduction in spending on asylum would have on the Scottish Government's block grant.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818778, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64446", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Leader of Dundee City Council can expect to receive a response to his letter dated 14 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818786, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64445", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when her Department plans to respond to the consultation on the Oil and gas price mechanism, which closed on 28 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818785, "askingMemberId": 4357, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64444", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he plans to respond to the consultation on Building the North Sea\u2019s Energy Future, which closed on 30 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818802, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to tackle child poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818802", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818672, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to help reduce tensions between Armenia and Azerbaijan; and what steps he is taking to promote respect for freedom of religion or belief in efforts to", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818671, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to ensure a wide roll out the Family Hubs programme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818670, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to roll out integrated family hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818669, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the White Paper entitled Restoring control over the immigration system, published on 12 May 2025, when she plans to publish the (a) eligibility criteria and (b) application process f", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818668, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of people with non-alcoholic fatty liver disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818667, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an estimate of the number of first-time buyers in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818770, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64436", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the F-35 programme partner nations on Israel\u2019s (a) compliance with international humanitarian law and (b) use of F", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818869, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of research funding models, in the context of the forthcoming national cancer plan; and whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of rese", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818868, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase screening programmes to improve early diagnosis of cancers, in the context of the forthcoming National Cancer Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818866, "askingMemberId": 4118, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of integrating smoking cessation services into (a) A&E, (b) mental health services and (c) lung screening.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818769, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business and Trade of 1 July 2025 in the debate on Hospitality Sector, Official Report, column 81WH, when he pl", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818768, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business and Trade of 1 July 2025 in the debate on Hospitality Sector, Official Report, column 81WH, if he will", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818767, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Business and Trade of 1 July 2025 in the debate on Hospitality Sector, Official Report, column 81WH, what the m", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818756, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-09T00:00:00", "uin": "64429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to continue the children's hospice grant beyond March 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818738, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-10T00:00:00", "uin": "64428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how much funding has been allocated to the Post Office in each year of the 2025 Spending Review period.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818864, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2025 to Question 58982 on Information Commissioner's Office: Wilmslow, if he will publish the Information Commissioner\u2019s Office's commercial analysis o", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818863, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2025 to Question 58982 on Information Commissioner's Office: Wilmslow, what steps his Department took to find alternative office space for the Informat", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818846, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the UK Health Security Agency news announcement of 21 May 2025, how much he has spent on testing mosquitoes through the Vector-Borne Real-time Arbovirus Detection and", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818728, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to help ensure that the (a) financial and (b) related professional services industry is represented on the Defence Industrial Joint Council.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818794, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, when he plans to respond to the consultation entitled Building the North Sea\u2019s energy future which closed on 30 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818793, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will discuss the position of contractor employees at Wood Group with trade union signatories to the Energy Services Agreement.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818792, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the viability of the Wood Group\u2019s North Sea oil and gas contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818739, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64420", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Oral Statement of 30 October 2024 on Financial Statement and Budget Report, Official Report, column 821, whether it remains her policy not to extend the freeze on income tax thresholds.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818737, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it remains her Department's policy to spend an additional \u00a31 billion on employment support for people with health conditions and disabilities by 2029-30 relative to pre-Spring Statement plans, f", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818865, "askingMemberId": 3912, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64418", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the ongoing review of the customs treatment of low-value imports on tax revenue.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818819, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated to family hubs for each year of the Spending Review 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818819", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818818, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to oblige local authorities to provide family hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818818", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818817, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of publishing a national outcomes framework for family hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818817", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818816, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Child Poverty Taskforce on family hubs, in the context of the development of the Child Poverty Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818816", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818815, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Family Hubs programme is available across England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818815", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818810, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of family hubs on (a) neighbourhood health and (b) the delivery of integrated community-based health services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818810", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818809, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report by Barnardo's entitled Building Families, Building Futures, published on 24 June 2025, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing family hubs ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818809", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818725, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the prevalence of gambling among the prison population; and what steps she is taking to help tackle gambling-related issues in prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818704, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for its policies of recent reports of the (a) detention and (b) deportation of members of the Baha'i com", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818703, "askingMemberId": 1593, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to his Nigerian counterpart on the killing of over 200 Christians in Yelewata on 19 June 2025; and what diplomatic steps he is taking to help", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818851, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to answer Question 59988, tabled on 16 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818849, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when he plans to answer Question 61737, tabled on 23 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818677, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64405", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she expects to receive the conclusions of the Payment Vision Delivery Committee.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818727, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64404", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were waiting for treatment from community mental health services in the West Midlands in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818726, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) male and (b) female ex-offenders found employment within six months of release in the West Midlands in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818791, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to (a) encourage the installation of heat pumps and (b) ensure that homes are properly insulated to support the effective operation of those heat pumps.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818790, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to increase the number of electric vehicle charging stations in (a) Preston, (b) Lancashire and (c) the North West.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818789, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions for manslaughter there have been in (a) Lancashire, (b) Greater Manchester and (c) Liverpool in cases involving suicide where domestic abuse was a contributing factor.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818867, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the size of the badger population in (a) Lincolnshire and (b) the East Midlands.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818855, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications have been rejected on the grounds of unknown nationality in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818852, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications have been rejected on the grounds of disputed nationality in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818777, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will provide additional funding for pothole repair in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818751, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to ensure improved access to schooling for children with (a) visual and (b) hearing impairments in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818749, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what dates she has raised small boat crossings with the European Commission since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818862, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer 30 June 2025 of Question 58911 on Vaccine Damage Payment Scheme: Coronavirus, if he will set out a timetable for completion of the (a) consideration of options and (b) recomm", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818850, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64392", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Exchequer Secretary to the Treasury plans to respond to the correspondence from the hon. Member for Christchurch of 3 April 2025, reference MC2025/08032.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818747, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timeline is for implementing measures in Inshore Marine Protected Areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818746, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timeline is for the implementation of the stage 3 offshore MPA byelaws once the consultation has been concluded.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818742, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of England's waters would be closed to bottom trawling when the proposed stage 3 byelaws are implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818740, "askingMemberId": 146, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department adopted the features-based approach for the assessment method for the stage 3 Marine Protected Area byelaws.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818683, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 30 June 2025 on Nuclear Test Veteran Records Exercise and the Merlin Database, HCWS748, if he will publish the findings gathered from the 43,000 files which have already been ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818680, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 30 June 2025 on Nuclear Test Veteran Records Exercise and the Merlin Database, HCWS748, for what reason the Individual Medical Records of military personnel who participated i", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818569, "askingMemberId": 5264, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made by the expert panel of clinical specialists on its review of the harms caused to young people by the provision of unregulated cross-sex hormones by private providers; an", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818568, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with Natural England on the potential merits of increasing access to nature in order to benefit physical and mental health.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Outdoor Recreation: Health", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818567, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support creative industries in Leeds North West constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arts: Leeds North West", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818566, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to improve student access to apprenticeships.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Apprentices: Students", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818565, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64381", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to (a) ensure that AI sources used in schools are (i) accurate and (ii) credible and (b) support children to use AI effectively.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818564, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of mental health conditions among young people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818563, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to insulin for people who need it.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Insulin", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818562, "askingMemberId": 5260, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has allocated for the provision of insulin pumps for local services in the (a) 2025-26 and (b) 2026-27 financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Diabetes: Medical Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818561, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to support victims of crimes committed using social media in (a) Eastbourne and (b) the South East.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: Victims", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818560, "askingMemberId": 5187, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment her Department has made on the potential merits of using (a) local and (b) regional newspapers for government advertising.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Local Press", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818559, "askingMemberId": 5187, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the ADHD taskforce in helping to reduce waiting lists for ADHD treatment in (a) Hertford and Stortford constituency, (b) Hertf", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818558, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had discussions with the Scottish Government on the withdraw funding for Veterans First Point Lothian.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans First Point: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818557, "askingMemberId": 5271, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ratify the Global Oceans Treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Biodiversity Beyond National Jurisdiction Agreement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818556, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64372", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of recognising (a) mental health conditions and (b) learning difficulties as distinct protected characteristics.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Illness and Learning Disability: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818555, "askingMemberId": 5316, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department plans to take to support the expansion of consumer options for low-carbon heating systems for households that are unable to install a heat pump.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heating: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818554, "askingMemberId": 5318, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to consult health professionals as part of the changes to the Carr-Hill formula funding model for GP practices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818553, "askingMemberId": 5316, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64369", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to update the guidance for Approved Document F of the Building Regulations to recognise smart ventilation systems as a compliant option for homes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818552, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64368", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to help reduce waiting times for referrals to the Pensions Ombudsman for people in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions Ombudsman: Yeovil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818551, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of recent trends in the number of referrals to the Pensions Ombudsman in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions Ombudsman: Yeovil", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818550, "askingMemberId": 5321, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is considering to help tackle potential transnational repression of (a) Hong Kong, (b) Uyghur and (c) Tibetan diaspora communities in the UK, in the con", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chinese Embassy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818539, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64365", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his international counterparts on the recognition of a Palestinian state.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestinians: Recognition of States", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818538, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help ensure that the transport system supports economic growth in Warrington South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: Warrington South", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818537, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64363", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to help improve the (a) financial oversight and (b) delivery assurance of major infrastructure projects.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infrastructure: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818536, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64362", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support capital funding for Broomfield's leisure centre in Warrington South constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leisure Centres: Warrington South", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818535, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress she has made on closing contingency hotels used to accommodate asylum seekers in Warrington.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Warrington", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818534, "askingMemberId": 5180, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64360", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of lifting the trade embargo on the Turkish Republic of Northern Cyprus.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818533, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps with local authorities to that ensure travel distance is taken into account when (a) calculating school catchment zones and (b) offering school places.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818532, "askingMemberId": 5180, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what diplomatic steps his Department is taking to support a political solution in Cyprus .", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818531, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with Public Health England and the UK Health Security Agency on the use of mercury in dental amalgam fillings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Mercury", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818530, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64356", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Commission is taking to support the work of the House of Commons Table Office; and what assessment the Commission has made of the contributi", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Table Office", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818529, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2025 to Question 36916 on British Overseas Territories: Companies, what discussions he has had with the British Virgin Islands government o", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818528, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to (a) reduce pensioner poverty and (b) increase pension benefit uptake.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensioners: Poverty and Social Security Benefits", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818527, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64353", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of pubs in (a) supporting community wellbeing and (b) tackling social isolation.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Houses: Health and Loneliness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818526, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64352", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to hold discussions with representatives of the brewing and pub sector on how to (a) create growth and (b) reduce barriers to investment, before the Autumn Budget 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer and Public Houses: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818525, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64351", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the cumulative impact of changes to (a) business rates and (b) employer National Insurance contributions on the financial viability of (i) pubs and (ii) breweries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer and Public Houses: Business Rates and Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818524, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64350", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to consult representatives from the (a) beer and (b) pub sectors ahead of the next Budget.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer and Public Houses: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818523, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64349", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to reduce beer duty.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818522, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64348", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment she has made of beer duty in (a) the UK and (b) other European countries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818521, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64347", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the number of jobs supported by the beer and pub sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer and Public Houses: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818520, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64346", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to consult representatives from the beer and pub sector ahead of the Autumn Budget 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Beer and Public Houses: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818519, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on ensuring the delivery of (a) baby formula and (b) other essential humanitarian aid into Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Humanitarian Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818518, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will take steps to ensure that community benefit payments from renewable energy developments are spent on (a) housing, (b) reducing levels of fuel poverty and (c) social care.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818517, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of applying a statutory 2% gross revenue contribution requirement to existing renewable energy projects over 1MW in capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818516, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of allocating a proportion of gross revenues from offshore renewable energy projects to local authority infrastructure funds.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818515, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of (a) Denmark\u2019s Promotion of Renewable Energy Act 2008 and (b) other international models for statutory comm", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818514, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what estimate he has made of the total value of community benefit payments made by (a) onshore and (b) offshore renewable energy projects in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818513, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent discussions he has had with renewable energy developers on establishing a statutory framework for community benefit payments based on a proportion of gross revenue.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818512, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to encourage consistent revenue-based contributions to community benefit schemes by onshore renewable developments.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818511, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what contracts their Department has with Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818510, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 62450 on Vamorolone, which NHS Trusts have submitted prior approval forms.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818509, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken to process rural payments.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Subsidies", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818508, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate her Department has made of the levels of noise pollution on roads (a) in Oxfordshire and (b) nationally.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818507, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to NHS occupational therapists involved in Disabled Facilities Grants for (a) children and (b) other people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818506, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a statutory minimum revenue contribution from newly consented renewable energy developments to community benefit funds.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818505, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help protect supermarket delivery drivers from (a) threats, (b) abuse and (c) violence.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Delivery Services: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818503, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Government\u2019s proposed Bill discount scheme of up to \u00a32,500 over 10 years for those living up to 500m from new and significantly upgra", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818502, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of community benefit packages from new renewable energy infrastructure projects on Inverness, Skye, and West Ross-shire constit", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy: Inverness, Skye and West Ross-shire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818501, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent discussions his Department has had with SSEN Transmission on community benefits.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "SSEN", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818500, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contracts their Department has with Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818499, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress her Department has made on tackling antisocial behaviour in (a) Beckenham and Penge constituency and (b) across England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anti-social Behaviour", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818498, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64324", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contracts their Department has with Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818497, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what contracts their Department has with Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818496, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps with Cabinet colleagues to remove the two-child benefit cap as part of the Tackling Child Poverty strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818495, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contracts their Department has with Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818494, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what contracts their Department has with Palantir.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Palantir", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818493, "askingMemberId": 5132, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress her Department has made on improving neighbourhood policing (a) in Beckenham and Penge constituency and (b) elsewhere in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neighbourhood Policing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818492, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64318", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure (a) the timely availability of pollution data, (b) that water companies are held to account for sewage discharges and (c) that improvements to storm o", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water: Pollution", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818491, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps has she taken to ensure (a) fairness and (b) transparency in the allocation of social housing.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818490, "askingMemberId": 5161, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to ensure that (a) violent offenders and (b) people convicted of grievous bodily harm resulting in life-changing injuries are not inappropriately released early under existing early release", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisoners' Release", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818489, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to take steps to improve access to minimally-processed foods for (a) all consumers and (b) children and young people.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Processed Food", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818488, "askingMemberId": 5134, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals to automatically limit a surviving parent's parental responsibility over their child in cases where one parent has unlawfully killed the other.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homicide: Parents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818487, "askingMemberId": 5145, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) dogs and (b) cats were imported non commercially under the PETS Directive in each month of 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818486, "askingMemberId": 5145, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) dogs and (b) cats were imported under commercial rules under the Ballai Directive in each month of 2024; and from which country.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818485, "askingMemberId": 5262, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to adopt the provisions set out in Annex XVI of Regulation (EU) 2017/745 on products without an intended medical purpose.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medical Equipment: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818484, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what his planned timetable is for the consultation on the British industrial competitiveness scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Industry: Trade Competitiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818483, "askingMemberId": 5278, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2025 to Question 60276 on Development Aid, when he expects to complete the resource allocation process.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818482, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the system of recording abuse against roadworkers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Works: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818481, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of dormant assets funds will be allocated to youth services.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dormant Assets Scheme: Youth Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818480, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of removing the Universal Credit health element on claimants under the age of 22.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818479, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64305", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that people with mental health conditions are not disproportionately disadvantaged by the proposed reforms to PIP.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Mental Illness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818478, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the registration dates for industry under UK REACH.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818477, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish his Department's strategy for (a) the chemicals industry and (b) chemicals management.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818476, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to respond to the consultation on the UK REACH Alternative Transitional Registration model (ATRm) for chemicals.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818475, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department had with the Paymaster General regarding UK-EU trade and environmental standards prior to the UK-EU summit in London on 18 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Protection and Trade Agreements: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818474, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to include discussions on the future co-operation on chemical regulations in the annual UK-EU summits.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818473, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether closer co-operation on chemical regulations was discussed at the UK-EU Summit on 18 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818472, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64298", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has had discussions with the Prudential Regulation Authority on the potential impact of reforming Solvency UK on the availability of annuity capital for investment in (a) housing, (b) transport and (c) i", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Insolvency: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818471, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to ensure that Homes England will take a strategic approach to affordable rural housing delivery by embedding the needs of the countryside at all levels ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818470, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increasing the breadth of subjects students study at A-Level on (a) life chances, (b) employability and (c) the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GCE A-level", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818469, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the current maths curriculum in the context of increasing demand for data skills.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mathematics: Curriculum", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818468, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve the UK\u2019s PISA mathematics performance.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mathematics: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818467, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the gap between the lowest and highest achievers in GCSE maths performance.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mathematics: GCSE", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818466, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure more students from less affluent areas are taught by trained maths teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mathematics: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818465, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to continue funding tennis facilities following the conclusion of the Park Tennis Project.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tennis: Facilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818464, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64290", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to invest in (a) tennis, (b) padel and (c) court-base sports in the 2025-2026 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sports: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818463, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) Newcastle-under-Lyme constituency and (b) other communities have access to covered tennis facilities to enable year-round play.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tennis: Facilities", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818462, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64288", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he plans to review standing charges on electricity bills for households on prepayment meters.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electricity: Standing Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818461, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64287", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support is available to local environmental groups undertaking citizen science river testing.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rivers: Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818460, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64286", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the current NHS dentist vacancy rate is in Surrey; and what steps he is taking to ensure equitable dental care access in Epsom and Ewell constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dental Services: Surrey", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818459, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64285", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much bus companies are reimbursed per journey for disabled bus pass holders; and whether this is a fixed rate across regions.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Concessions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818458, "askingMemberId": 5256, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64284", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty notices have the police issued to people smoking in private vehicles in which children are present (a) in total and (b) in each year since this became an offence.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Smoking", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818457, "askingMemberId": 5256, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many young people accessed the Music and Dance Scheme in each of the last five academic years; and how many students will be supported by the scheme in the academic year 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dance and Music: Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818456, "askingMemberId": 5186, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of prioritising NHS jobs for British citizens who have gained medical qualifications (a) within the UK and (b) from institutions within other Eur", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818455, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make it her policy review the level of fines that local authorities can levy in relation to illegal parking.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking Offences: Fines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818454, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what current restrictions are placed upon tourist visitors from China.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Entry Clearances: China", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818453, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64279", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of introducing new restrictions on developers who have a history of bankcruptcy on the housing sector.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Property Development: Bankcruptcy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818452, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the readiness of the chemicals sector for the 2026 UK REACH registration deadline for substances over 1,000 metric tonnes; and whether", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chemicals: Regulation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818451, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64277", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will provide an update on when HM Revenue & Customs will restart processing IHT30 clearance requests.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818450, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64276", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of job losses at (a) Bournemouth University and (b) the wider higher education sector on the (i) quality of education and (ii) range of courses availab", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Higher Education: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818449, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64275", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact on (a) energy efficiency and (b) indoor air quality of adding mechanical ventilation with heat recovery systems to the list of energy saving materials eligible ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818448, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64274", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has made an assessment of the potential implications for his polices on the wellbeing of children of the level of effectiveness of the Online Safety Amendment (Social Media M", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Media: Australia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818447, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Centre for Young Lives report, entitled Everything to Play For, published in June 2025, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of decline in the duration of free playtime dur", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Play: School Day", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818446, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the potential merits of integrating health and social care services with access to welfare advice.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Security Benefits: Advisory Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818445, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the annual saving to the public purse from not fully disregarding (a) War Pensions and (b) Armed Forces Compensation Scheme payments in the assessment of Pension", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818444, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its fraud strategy provides consumers with protection from all types of fraudulent advertising.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Advertising: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818443, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of (a) a hub and spoke model and (b) the utilisation of detached youth work within Young Futures Hubs on (i) outreach and (ii) access for yo", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818442, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64268", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress her Department has made towards establishing a ban on conversion practices.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Conversion Therapy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818441, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how local areas will be supported to implement Young Futures Hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young Futures Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818440, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether investment in family hubs will be included in the upcoming Child Poverty Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Hubs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818439, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the interpretation of the definition of Grey Belt by planning inspectors in (a) rural and (b) semi-rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Belt: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818438, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the implementation of Grey Belt policy aligns with the settlement hierarchy set out in adopted local plans.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Belt: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818437, "askingMemberId": 5201, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to issue planning practice guidance on the (a) use and (b) interpretation of Grey Belt policy.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Green Belt", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818436, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the 2013 mandate to accurately collect and collate data on cancer recurrence is being fully implemented.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818435, "askingMemberId": 5256, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of including capital purchase costs for the acquisition of (a) run-down or (b) former cultural venues within the eligibility criteria of the C", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Culture: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818434, "askingMemberId": 5256, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much has been raised for grassroot music venues to date via the voluntary ticket levy; and what steps her Department plans to take monitor progress of the grassroots ticket levy.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818433, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of expanding the eligibility criteria for the Motability Scheme to include Attendance Allowance claimants.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motability: Attendance Allowance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818432, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the accessibility of the new Companies House identity verification system; who pays for the third-party ID verification service connected to t", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818431, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support pensioners who have (a) become disabled after reaching State Pension age and (b) require (i) adapted vehicles and (ii) mobility assistance.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensioners: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818430, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the resilience of the water supply in the long term in Plymouth.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply: Plymouth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818429, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many water supply outages there were in Plymouth in (a) 2022, (b) 2023, (c) 2024 and (d) 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Water Supply: Plymouth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818428, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with local authorities on the variances in the eligibility criteria for disabled bus passes.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Concessions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818427, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps her Department has taken to support disabled people using public transport.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818426, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64252", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has a target for narrowing the disability employment gap.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equal Pay: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818425, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64251", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the potential impact of early years support on long-term mental health barriers to employment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Mental Illness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818424, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64250", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of proposals by the French Government to allow the interception of small boats? up to 300 metres from shore on the number of small boats crossing t", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818423, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64249", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of pupils learning modern foreign languages to GCSE level in Bournemouth.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Languages: GCSE", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818422, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64248", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the number of gambling adverts on people living in Bolton North East constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818421, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many gambling adverts were published in each year from 2019 to 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818420, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64246", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of long-term mental health conditions starting in childhood on employment rates amongst those young people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Mental Illness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818419, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64245", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of mental health services in (a) Bournemouth and (b) Dorset.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Dorset", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818418, "askingMemberId": 5208, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64244", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will set out the terms of reference for the consultation on the British industrial competitiveness scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Industry: Trade Competitiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818417, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the proposals on gambling outlined in the letter sent to him by the Health and Social Care Committee on 8 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818416, "askingMemberId": 5095, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of gambling adverts on people living in Bolton North East constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818415, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people living in Essex who are digitally excluded have full access to the healthcare services they need.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Essex", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818414, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help increase the uptake of Shared Parental Leave.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parental Leave", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818413, "askingMemberId": 5138, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase the uptake of statutory paternity leave.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Paternity Leave", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818412, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support research into dyscalculia.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Dyscalculia: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818411, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate he has made of the potential impact of the play industry on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children's Play", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818410, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she is taking steps to encourage local authorities to buy playground equipment from UK manufacturers.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Playgrounds: Equipment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818409, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the use of hotels as accommodation for asylum seekers on the (a) hospitality and (b) tourism sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818408, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that integrated care boards (a) commission children\u2019s palliative care and (b) fund children\u2019s hospices in (i) an equitable and (ii) a sustainable way.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818407, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to (a) continue to provide financial support for children's hospices and (b) increase the level of funding in line with (i) inflation and (ii) rises in costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818406, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of asylum seekers being housed in hotels in (a) Bournemouth and (b) the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818405, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64231", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to improve support for young trans people under the age of 18.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transgender People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818404, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department (a) has made and (b) plans to make an assessment of the impact of exposure to chemicals on cancer incidence rates.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818403, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to provide routine access to circulating tumour DNA blood tests to support the (a) detection and (b) treatment of breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818402, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the National Audit of Metastatic Breast Cancer will provide a specific breakdown by (a) breast cancer subtype and (b) hormone receptor status.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818401, "askingMemberId": 5329, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS spends on average per patient with secondary (metastatic) breast cancer; and if he will make a comparative assessment of the average spend per patient with primary breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818400, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department plans to take steps to help support domestic manufacturing of playground equipment.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Playgrounds: Manufacturing Industries", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818399, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish her Department's White Paper on reforms to the SEND system.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Educational Needs: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818398, "askingMemberId": 5184, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of online misinformation in the use of chlorine dioxide in treatments for autism on people with autism; and what steps he plans to ta", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chlorine Dioxide: Autism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818397, "askingMemberId": 5210, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veteran ID cards have been issued to veterans who were discharged before December 2018, by council area.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Identity Cards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818396, "askingMemberId": 5184, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making (a) court transcription services (i) cheaper and (ii) more accessible for the families of victims and (b) court recordings directly available to thos", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Law Reporting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818395, "askingMemberId": 5184, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64221", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether recordings of court proceedings from October 2023 onwards are available for transcription for a period of one year.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Law Reporting", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818394, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether local authorities will be required to provide funding towards infrastructure for New Towns.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "New Towns: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818393, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether ICBs will be expected to fund redundancy costs from re-organisation from their day-to-day budgets.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Integrated Care Boards: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818392, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ask NHS England to publish an analysis of the options they have considered for re-organisation of ICBs in the East of England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Integrated Care Boards: East of England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818391, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the expected population coverage of each ICB in England is following the proposed re-organisation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Integrated Care Boards: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818390, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the planned re-organisation of the BLMK ICB with (a) Hertfordshire and (b) Cambridgeshire & Peterborough on the provision of", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Wixams", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818389, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that ICBs effectively represent small and rural communities, in the context of the re-organisation of ICBs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Integrated Care Boards: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818388, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS employees have a level 7 apprenticeship qualification.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Apprentices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818387, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the press release entitled NHS leaders face both \u2018carrot and stick\u2019 in new performance drive, published on 15 May 2025, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Equal Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818386, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to publish a social care workforce strategy, in the context of the White Paper entitled Restoring control over the immigration system, published on 12 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Social Services: Migrant Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818385, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64211", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date the powers to make compulsory purchases of land for HS2 Phase 2a purposes expire.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818384, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64210", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of the press release by the United Nations Human Rights Office entitled Agreement between Mauriti", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818383, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64209", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his Moroccan counterpart on ensuring human rights for the Sahrawi people.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Western Sahara: Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818382, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64208", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his Egyptian counterpart on the seizure of St. Catherine\u2019s Monastery.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Egypt: Religious Orders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818381, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64207", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2025 to Question 55512 on Flood Control: Owner Occupation, how much funding (a) his Department and (b) the Environment Agency have allocated for promot", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Owner Occupation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818380, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64206", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2025 to Question 55512 on Flood Control: Owner Occupation, if he will direct the Environment Agency to hold a community engagement event on flood risk ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Owner Occupation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818379, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64205", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on the Chilterns National Landscape Boundary Review project.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chilterns: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818378, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64204", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has made an estimate of the potential impact of the Parthenon Marbles on the economic value of tourism.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parthenon Sculptures: Tourism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818377, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64203", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had recent discussions with the Chair of the British Museum on the Parthenon Marbles.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parthenon Sculptures", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818376, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64202", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to create a single public reporting service for problems at (a) local and (b) national government level.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Bodies: Complaints", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818375, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64201", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) unauthorised and (b) sickness absences there were in the civil service in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Sick Leave", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818374, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64200", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the level of UK investment generated by the GREAT campaign since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GREAT: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818373, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to his Department's consultation Extending the UK Emissions Trading Scheme cap beyond 2030, published on 12 February 2025, when the Government's response will be published.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Emissions Trading Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818372, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64198", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on conditions attached to the spending of the farming budget to ensure (a) value for money, (b) increased food ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818371, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timetable is for publication of the revised Environmental Improvement Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818370, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the time taken to introduce the due diligence scheme for forest risk commodities enabled by schedule 17 of the Environment Act 20", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Forests: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818369, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that the process of appointing the new Chair of the Office for Environmental Protection protects its independence.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Office for Environmental Protection: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818368, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the farming budget is used to meet legally-binding (a) environmental targets under the Environment Act 2021 and (b) emissions reduction ta", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818367, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the (a) Landscape Recovery and (b) Higher Tier Countryside Stewardship schemes will be re-opened for applications.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Countryside Stewardship Scheme and Landscape Recovery Scheme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818366, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much and what proportion of capital spending on flooding will be allocated to (a) hard infrastructure and (b) nature-based solutions.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Capital Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818365, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on the pursuit of a (a) deployable and (b) persistent wide area anti-submarine warfare search capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Antisubmarine Warfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818364, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 62328 on Unitary Councils, when will the statutory consultation period for proposed unitary councils in Cambridgeshire begin.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818363, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the suitability of the (a) substation connection and (b) grid capacity to support capacity of up to 4,500 homes at the MOD Trailblazer site at RAF", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "RAF Wyton: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818362, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64188", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what date (a) was the last and (b) is the next meeting of the Honours and Appointments Secretariat.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Honours and Appointments Secretariat", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818361, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of calculating student loan repayments on an annual basis to prevent overpayments.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Loans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818360, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64186", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2025 to Question 57896 on Funeral Payments, how many applicants (a) responsible for funeral costs and (b) in receipt of a qualifying benefit did not receive a social fu", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Funeral Payments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818359, "askingMemberId": 5092, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64185", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if the Government will take steps to recognise the state of Palestine as part of its efforts to seek (a) peace and (b) a lasting two state solution in the region.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818358, "askingMemberId": 5092, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64184", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help ensure the adequacy of the number of police officers in Merseyside police.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Merseyside Police", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818357, "askingMemberId": 5092, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to help tackle child poverty in St Helens North constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818356, "askingMemberId": 5092, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to (a) help children with dyslexia and (b) improve the availability of early screening.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Dyslexia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818355, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64181", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has had recent discussions with South Western Rail on the role of open access rail operators in supporting (a) connectivity, (b) passenger choice and (c) service quality within the UK rail network.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Train Operating Companies: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818354, "askingMemberId": 5297, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64180", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the requirement for applicants to demonstrate three years of continuous residence in the UK to be considered for civil service roles on t", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818353, "askingMemberId": 5303, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64179", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) people and (b) groups have been prosecuted by the Environment Agency for damaging (i) watercourses and (ii) rivers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inland Waterways and Rivers: Damage", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818352, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64178", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on corporate governance.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Corporate Governance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818351, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the petition entitled Introduction of a business, human rights and environment act, submitted to his Department on 19 June ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business: Environment Protection and Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818350, "askingMemberId": 5147, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to ensure that the non-pipeline transport of CO2 for offshore storage does not cause marine pollution.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818549, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing foster carers with the same legal status as (a) health workers and (b) teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foster Care", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818548, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support the mental health of (a) victims and (b) survivors of crime.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: Victims", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818547, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase funding for training in (a) Sussex Police and (b) other local police forces.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818546, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the UK\u2013India Free Trade Agreement on his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818545, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help support the recruitment of teachers in (a) Eastbourne constituency and (b) East Sussex.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818544, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support the provision and availability of vocational educational programmes for pupils across Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vocational Education: Eastbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818543, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to help support people with childcare costs in Eastbourne constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818542, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64168", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the increased funding for employment support will be allocated to the hospitality sector in coastal towns.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: Coastal Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818541, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64167", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to help support economic growth in the hospitality sector in coastal towns.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitality Industry: Coastal Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818540, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64166", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department plans to introduce additional support measures for businesses affected by increases in National Insurance Contributions in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employers' Contributions: Eastbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818347, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64165", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of a reduction in the annual tax-free cash ISA allowance on people in (a) Eastbourne and (b) the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Individual Savings Accounts", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818346, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the National Underground Asset Register on roadworks in Broxbourne constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Underground Asset Register: Road Works", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818344, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-16T00:00:00", "uin": "64163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what plans his Department has to for hydrogen-related funding in (a) Bradford East constituency and (b) West Yorkshire, in the context of his Department's Net Zero Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818343, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much of the UK humanitarian aid budget has been spent on projects relating to support for Rohingya in Cox\u2019s Bazar, Bangladesh, since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818342, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle cold calls; and whether he plans to introduce financial penalties on people conducting cold calls.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Direct Selling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818341, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64160", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are affected by the Loan Charge that have open pre-2010 enquiries.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818340, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64159", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have settled with HMRC to avoid the Loan Charge.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818339, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64158", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the number of people impacted by the Loan Charge Scandal.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tax Avoidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818338, "askingMemberId": 5051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of taking steps to help ensure that the transition of children from foster care to adoption does not have a detrimental impact to the (a) children and (b) fo", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818337, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-09T00:00:00", "uin": "64156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support community-based knife crime prevention programmes in Bradford.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818336, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64155", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to expand access to community-based rehabilitation services.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Rehabilitation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818335, "askingMemberId": 4394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64154", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment her Department has made of trends in the level of (a) staffing and (b) caseloads in the probation service.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818334, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support local media in(a) Eastbourne constituency and (b) East Sussex.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Press: East Sussex", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818333, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support seaside tourism in Eastbourne constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tourism: Eastbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818332, "askingMemberId": 5040, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to take steps to update regulations on the (a) composition, (b) marketing and (c) labelling of commercial (i) infant and (ii) toddler foods.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infant Foods: Marketing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818331, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in reference to the Migration Advisory Committee report published on 10 June 2025, what assessment she has  made of the potential merits of (a) revising and (b) lowering the family visa financial requ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818330, "askingMemberId": 4623, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the Lawn Tennis Association on the provision of funding for (a) tennis and (b) padel facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tennis: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818329, "askingMemberId": 4860, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish the (a) justice impact test and (b) new burdens assessment her Department has undertaken on the Renters\u2019 Rights Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renters' Rights Bill ", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818314, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support jobseekers in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: Eastbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818313, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help support the farming industry in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Eastbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818312, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64145", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will publish an assessment of the economic impact of legally binding net zero targets on infrastructure investment in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infrastructure: Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818311, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to support the energy efficiency of homes in Eastbourne.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818309, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to support people living in fuel poverty in Eastbourne constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fuel Poverty: Eastbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818308, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to support clean energy initiatives in Eastbourne constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Clean Energy: Eastbourne", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818307, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that services provided through the Buy with Confidence Scheme complete satisfactory work.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trading Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818306, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to support single parents to secure affordable accommodation suitable for their children following a separation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Lone Parents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818305, "askingMemberId": 4617, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64139", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it remains her Department's policy to (a) phase out the sale of new petrol and diesel vehicles by 2030 and (b) ensure that all new car sales are for Zero Emission Vehicles by 2035.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818304, "askingMemberId": 5050, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of foreign national offenders who have attempted to return to the UK after being deported.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offenders: Foreign Nationals", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818303, "askingMemberId": 5076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his Department's policies of (a) prosecutions of opposition party leaders and (b) levels of repression of civil ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Georgia: Civil Liberties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818302, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to raise awareness of the availability of Pension Credit this winter.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818284, "askingMemberId": 4753, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-08T00:00:00", "uin": "64135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to help improve mobile telephone signal in (a) Brancepeth Village, (b) County Durham and (c)) across the country.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818278, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) charged, (b) prosecuted and (c) convicted for human trafficking under the Modern Slavery Act 2015 in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818277, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64133", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies of Ofcom\u2019s proposals to remove the prohibitions on (a) matching rights and (b) bundling.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Broadcasting: Competition", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818276, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) charged, (b) prosecuted and (c) convicted for knowingly assisting asylum seekers to enter the UK under s25A Immigration Act 1971 in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818275, "askingMemberId": 4320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) charged, (b) prosecuted and (c) convicted for assisting unlawful immigration under s25 Immigration Act 1971 in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818274, "askingMemberId": 5061, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64130", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of a Central Finance Facility for credit unions on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Credit Unions: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818273, "askingMemberId": 5071, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the five-week wait for Universal Credit on (a) debt and (b) poverty levels.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818271, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the bus fare cap increase on passenger numbers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818270, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make it her policy to ensure bus fares do not increase above the rate of inflation following the bus fare cap increase.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818266, "askingMemberId": 5036, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has considered including supported internship provision in Skills England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Skills England: Unpaid Work", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818265, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support disabled people from lower socioeconomic groups to be more physically active.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Exercise: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818264, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the leisure facilities available for disabled people in Stockport constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leisure: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818263, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with (a) Network Rail and (b) Avanti West Coast on the quality of public toilets at Stockport station.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Stockport Station: Public Lavatories", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818262, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make it her policy to extend Project?Reach to Stockport railway station.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways: Optical Fibres", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818261, "askingMemberId": 4811, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timetable is for publication of the animal welfare strategy; and if he will make it his Department's policy to ban male chick culling as part of the strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poultry: Animal Welfare", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818260, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to review the criteria for which applications to join the British Army are rejected on medical grounds.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818259, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle expressions of support for (a) Hamas and (b) Hezbollah at universities.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818258, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64118", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason there are currently no service standards in place for Family route visa applications.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818257, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to hold discussions with Vice Chancellors on the effectiveness of disciplinary procedures in tackling antisemitism at universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818256, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much and what proportion of funding the National-Level Transport Scheme allocates to the (a) investigation and (b) completion of business cases; and to the immediate construction of schemes that are ready t", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818255, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64115", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to replace the business rates system from 2026-27; and whether she plans to hold a consultation to inform the new system.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818254, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64114", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of increases in employer National Insurance contributions on the (a) fiscal position and (b) sustainability of independent SMEs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses: Employers' Contributions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818253, "askingMemberId": 5036, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of additional physiotherapists required to support people (a) with long-term health conditions and (b) who are disabled get back to work.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment: Chronic Illnesses and Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818252, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to (a) the UN and (b) other international bodies on the need for protection of civilians during the Sudan conflict.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818251, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what recent discussions he has had with independent SMEs on the impact of his Department's policies.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Small Businesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818250, "askingMemberId": 5036, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to ensure clinical leadership and advice is available within his Department for (a) Musculoskeletal conditions, (b) stroke, (c) neurological conditions, (d) cardiovascul", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818249, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to the warring parties in Sudan about the protection of civilians.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Armed Conflict", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818248, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has completed the capital review of transport projects.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Transport: Capital Investment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818247, "askingMemberId": 5061, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many schools have entrances which open directly onto a 70mph road in (a) the UK, (b) England and (c) the East of England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Roads: Schools", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818246, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the economic (a) stability and (b) powers of people involved in human rights abuses in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818245, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to launch a campaign to increase pension credit uptake before winter 2025-2026.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Credit: Publicity", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818244, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64104", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) places of worship and (b) religious sites (i) damaged and (ii) destroyed in Ukraine since February 2022; and whethe", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Religious Buildings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818243, "askingMemberId": 5036, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the level of need for additional (a) physiotherapists and (b) rehabilitation support workers in (i) the NHS and (ii) independent sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Physiotherapy: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818242, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 61897 on Responsible Dog Ownership Working Group, who the members of the taskforce are; which members are leading on each of the four", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Responsible Dog Ownership Working Group", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818241, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of good quality agricultural land being used for the development of large scale solar farms.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818240, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of school career services in (a) highlighting and (b) encouraging apprenticeships.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Vocational Guidance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818239, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to highlight the importance of safety at railway level crossings during the school summer holidays.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Level Crossings: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818238, "askingMemberId": 4657, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64098", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he has taken to sanction people involved in human rights abuses in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sudan: Human Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818237, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to ensure that local leaders work across county borders to ensure the (a) development and (b) sustainability of cross-border public transport services.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818236, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of demand responsive travel in rural areas in (a) the UK and (b) Leicestershire.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818235, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to provide funding for public transport in Leicestershire.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Transport: Leicestershire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818234, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2025 to Question 59764 on Chagos Islands: Sovereignty, what estimate he has made of the cost of payments to Mauritius for the (a) FCDO and (", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818232, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of reports about the treatment of (a) non-Orthodox and (b) minority faith groups in Ukrainian terri", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Ukraine", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818231, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what information his Department holds on the amount of income generated by the Ordnance Survey from public subscriptions in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ordnance Survey: Subscriptions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818230, "askingMemberId": 5030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will hold discussions with Ordance Survey on the potential merits of making the Ordnance Survey Maps Premium (a) service and (b) app available to the public for free.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818227, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2025 to Question 57460 on Policy, what her planned timetable is for the revision of the National Policy Statement on airport expansion.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airports: National Policy Statements", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818226, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has published guidance to local authorities on transferring internal council (a) personal data and (b) papers to political parties where such information i", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818224, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2025 to Question 56482 on Civil Service: London allowances, if she will take steps to ensure that the London weighted salaries for civil servant", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: London Allowance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818223, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Spending Review 2025, published on 11 June 2025, what assumptions have been made on the level of the (a) shire district, (b) police precept, (c) parish prec", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818222, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 12 June 2025 on Local Government Best Value, HCWS697, which (a) external individuals, (b) external organisations, (c) hon. Members and ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Cost Effectiveness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818220, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 May 2025 to Question 53573 on Oxford Growth Commission: Public Appointments, what the level of remuneration is for the Chair of the Oxford Growth Com", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oxford Growth Commission: Public Appointments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818219, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 May 2025 to Question 52627 on Night Time Industries Association, what correspondence her Department has received from the Night Time Industries Assoc", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Night Time Industries Association", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818217, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64083", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of Inheritance Tax provisions for agricultural property on farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818216, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2025 to Question 58054 on Fast Food, whether local authority powers under the National Planning Policy Framework to block new fast-food outlets ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fast Food: Planning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818214, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2025 to Question 57269 on Planning Permission, if she will introduce a policy requiring plain English in planning documents produced by her Depa", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission: Documents", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818213, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many Homes England staff are undergoing redeployment.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Homes England: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818212, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to her Department's press release entitled Rough sleeping to be decriminalised after 200 years, published on 10 June 2025, how the approach to a replacement regime", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sleeping Rough: Decriminalisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818211, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many endometriosis specialist practitioners there are in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Endometriosis: Health Professions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818210, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64077", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 55222 on Film: Business Rates, how many film studios in England will be subject to the higher multiplier on Rateable Values above \u00a3500,000, from April 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Film: Business Rates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818209, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64076", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 56711 on Council tax: valuation, how many complaints have been made to (a) Tier 1 complaints process, (b) Tier 2 complaints process and (c) the Adjudicator's Office ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax: Valuation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818207, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle online radicalisation in Northern Ireland; and whether she plans to introduce region-specific counter-extremism initiatives.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Radicalism: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818206, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to improve cyber resilience among (a) small businesses and (b) local authorities in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cybersecurity: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818205, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to promote careers in the Armed Forces among young people in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Career Development", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818204, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made a recent assessment of the potential role Northern Ireland-based industries might play in helping support the UK\u2019s nuclear (a) deterrent and (b) wider defence supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818203, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role Northern Ireland will play in the implementation of the Strategic Defence Review 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Strategic Defence Review: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818202, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Strategic Defence Review 2025, whether he plans to locate a munitions factory in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ammunition: Factories", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818201, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) prevent illegal migration into Northern Ireland via the Common Travel Area.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818200, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help support research into immunotherapy treatments for (a) pancreatic, (b) brain and (c) other difficult-to-treat cancers; and whether he plans to provide ad", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immunotherapy: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818199, "askingMemberId": 4857, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to ensure effective coordination between Government departments to tackle (a) the spread of child sexual abuse (i) material and (ii) harmful algorithms and (b) o", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Internet: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818198, "askingMemberId": 5055, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential conflict between the impact of exemptions to copyright law for AI development on the creative sector and the creative sector being listed ", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Arts: Economic Growth", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818197, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64065", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the National Security Adviser is (a) secretary of the National Security Council, (b) head of the National Security Secretariat and (c) Principal Accounting Officer for the Single Intelligence Account.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818196, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64064", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on appointing the new Conservative political member for the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818195, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Prime Minister\u2019s oral contribution of 4 June 2025, Official Report, Column 301, if he will provide evidential basis for his comment on China.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818194, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the impact of (a) dynamic pricing and (a) general payments on the (i) working conditions and (ii) pay of private hire drivers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Taxis: Conditions of Employment and Pay", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818193, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64061", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of bringing most unused pension funds within the value of a person\u2019s estate for Inheritance Tax purposes on people currently receiving pensions.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Funds: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818192, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to ban alcohol advertising.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818191, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what the planned (a) commencement and (b) implementation dates are for each substantive policy provision of the Employment Rights Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Rights Bill", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818190, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64058", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Business Secretary announces new DBT non-executive directors, published on 17 December 2024, if he will publish the correspondence to and from ", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Directors", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818189, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64057", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2024 to Question 54793 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, whether his Department's spending on the deal will count towards meeting the (a) 2.5 percent and (b) 3 perce", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818188, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2024 to Question 54793 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, what is the cash terms, monetary value of the Defence payment towards the Chagos deal in each individual yea", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818187, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64055", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2024 to Question 54793 on British Indian Ocean Territory: Sovereignty, what proportion of the costs will come from the (a) Ministry of Defence and (b) Foreign, Commonwealth and Devel", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sovereignty: Chagos Islands", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818186, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64054", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has a target for the number of staff it plans to employ over the period of the Spending Review.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818185, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's planned timetable is for publishing the set-up costs for the Deposit Return Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Deposit Return Schemes: Costs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818184, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to take to ensure that local authorities use funding from the Extended Producer Responsibility scheme to improve recycling provision.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recycling: Local Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818183, "askingMemberId": 4827, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ensure that funding derived from Extended Producer Responsibility fees will be ringfenced to support local authorities to improve their recycling provi", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Recycling: Local Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818166, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64050", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2025 to Question 57280 on Local Government: Reorganisation, what estimate she has made of the change in public sector net borrowing from local government reorganisation in each of t", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818165, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64049", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 54866 on Alcoholic Drinks, if she will remove the exclusion of the direct manufacture of alcoholic beverages from paragraph 2.12 of the UK Government Green Financing", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Alcoholic Drinks", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818164, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64048", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason council tax is not included in the measure of consumer price inflation.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Consumer Prices Index: Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818163, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64047", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2025 to Question 59321 on Police: Finance, what the grant funding to police is in cash terms in each financial year between 2024-25 and 2028-29.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818162, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2025 to Question 59314 on Local Government Finance, what the grant funding to local government is in cash terms in each financial year between 2", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818161, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to provide additional funding for the Terminally Ill Adults (End of Life) Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818158, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the adequacy of local authorities' Local Flood Risk Management Strategies.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Flood Control: Local Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818157, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of food security.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818156, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the disability pay gap.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Equal Pay: Disability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818155, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to help tackle violence against women and girls in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the rest of the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818154, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve awareness of symptoms of (a) lung and (b) pancreatic cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818153, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she is taking steps to introduce a GCSE on British Sign Language.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sign Language: GCSE", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818152, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department will take to improve digital infrastructure in rural schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Digital Technology", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818151, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to (a) tackle local authority financial deficits and (b) improve local authority value for money.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818150, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many homes have qualified for new boilers through Government energy schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Boilers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818349, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the UK\u2013India Free Trade Agreement on his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818348, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the UK\u2013India Free Trade Agreement on his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818170, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps he is taking to help protect (a) jobs and (b) supply chains which are dependent on British Steel.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Steel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818169, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether conditions were attached to the funding provided to British Steel to ensure (a) value for money and (b) long term sustainability.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818168, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the Steel Industry (Special Measures) Act 2025 and the \u00a394 million announced to save the Scunthorpe plant and British Steel, how much further funding has been provided to British Stee", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818326, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the UN Special Committee on Decolonization\u2019s 2025 session statement published in June 2025 (GA/C", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gibraltar: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818325, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the UN Special Committee on Decolonization\u2019s 2025 session Resolution adopted in June 2025 (GA/CO", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Falkland Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818324, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the UN on the (a) remit and (b) activities of the UN Special Committee on Decolonization.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UN Special Committee on Decolonisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818323, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the membership of the UN Special Committee on Decolonization on the decisions that it makes in respect of UK overseas t", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UN Special Committee on Decolonisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818322, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the resolution passed on the sovereignty of the Falkland Islands taken at the Organization of Am", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Falkland Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818321, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2025 to Question 60851 on Gibraltar: Sovereignty, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the sovereignty clause on Gibraltar", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gibraltar: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818320, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what funding requests his Department has received from the Government of Mauritius to support the establishment of a marine protected area in accordance with Article 5 of the", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Marine Protected Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818319, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how much funding from the public purse has been used to support the Marine Protected Area around the British Indian Ocean Territory in each year since 2010.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "British Indian Ocean Territory: Marine Protected Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818318, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in the Government of Mauritius on (i) the Chagossian Trust Fund and (ii) t", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818317, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the statement in the House of Lords of 30 June 2025, made by the Minister for Africa on the resettlement of Chagossians on the Chagos Archipelago and the Ch", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818316, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether operations conducted by special forces will be subject to the notifications requirements of paragraph 2 of Annex 1 of the UK-Mauritius Treaty.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818315, "askingMemberId": 4066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether papers from the previous Government were disclosed to Ministers in the Administration relating to the UK-Mauritius negotiations.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chagos Islands: Sovereignty", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818272, "askingMemberId": 4051, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of reports of disputes involving religious communities in the Bukovina region of Ukraine; an", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ukraine: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818228, "askingMemberId": 4030, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "64017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of out-of-town (a) taxi and (b) private hire vehicle licensing on local authority enforcement capabilities and pub", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818281, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with StandWithUs UK on its report entitled Voice of Students 2024-25, published on 7 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universities: Antisemitism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818233, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of (a) reports on the demolition of Ahmadiyya worship places, (b) the role of (i) Tehreek-e-Labbaik and (ii) extrem", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pakistan: Religious Freedom", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818328, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) strengthen national food security and (b) increase levels of domestic food production.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818327, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64013", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the proposed changes to Agricultural Property Relief and Business Property Relief on levels of food production.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818182, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64012", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2025 to Question 60037 on Dentistry: Higher Education, when he expects the Privy Council approval process to be completed.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "University of Portsmouth Dental Academy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818280, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made a comparative assessment of award rates for (a) in-person and (b) other modes of PIP assessment.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818279, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the award rate for Work Capability Assessment was (a) in-person, (b) not in-person and (c) across all modes in each of the last 10 years; and whether her Department has made a comparative assessmen", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818174, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people impacted by the changes to PIP proposed in the Universal Credit and Personal Independence Payment Bill she estimates will (a) lose eligibility to PIP entirely, (b)", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment and Universal Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818173, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Oral Statement of 30 June 2025 on Welfare Reform, columns 23-25, whether (a) the cost of changes to her welfare reform proposals include the cost of the new severe conditions group", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818172, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "64007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Oral Statement of 30 June 2025 on Welfare Reform, columns 23-25, what the evidential basis was for her statement that less that 1% of people on universal credit move into work each", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818300, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will expand the nuclear capabilities of the Royal Navy.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Navy: Nuclear Weapons", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818299, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to improve the air-to-air refuelling capabilities of the Royal Air Force.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Force: In-flight Refuelling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818298, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with his Irish counterpart on illegal immigration to the United Kingdom via that country.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Republic of Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818297, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to help reduce illegal immigration to the United Kingdom via the Republic of Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Republic of Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818296, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64002", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will reintroduce Lords Spiritual from the Church of Ireland to the House of Lords.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Church of Ireland: Bishops", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818295, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to work with relevant authorities to reduce the number of allergy related deaths in (a) England and (b) Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Allergies: Death", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818294, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "64000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to work with local authorities to reduce instances of fly-tipping.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fly-tipping", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818293, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Planning and Infrastructure Bill on National Parks and National Landscapes.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Landscapes and National Parks", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818292, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of Part 3 of the Planning and Infrastructure Bill on protected nature sites located within England\u2019s National Parks.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Parks: Planning", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818291, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken to support the (a) safety and (b) financial viability of black taxi drivers in London.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Taxis: Greater London", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818290, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken with relevant authorities to improve the safety of train drivers in (a) England and (b) Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Trains: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818289, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken to work with relevant authorities to improve the safety of bus drivers in (a) England and (b) Romford constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Buses: Safety", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818288, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the impact of regulation on small and medium-sized enterprises involved in the development and deployment of sustainable aviation fuel; and whether she plans to simplify relevant", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aviation: Alternative Fuels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818287, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the inclusion of small and medium-sized enterprises in procurement processes related to the development and supply of sustainable aviation fuel.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Aviation: Alternative Fuels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818345, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "63992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2025 to Question 62538 on State Retirement Pensions: Northern Ireland, what the total cost to the public purse was of all payments of the State Pension in Northern Irel", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818181, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "63991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps is he taking to support national campaigns which (a) raise awareness of glaucoma and (b) encourage regular eye tests for preventable sight loss conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818167, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "63990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 30 June to Questions 60413 and 61747 on Asylum: Northern Ireland, whether she plans to purchase (a) tower blocks and (b) student accommodation to house people claiming asylu", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818283, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average processing time was for asylum applications in the latest period for which data is available; and what steps her Department plans to take to reduce the time taken to process asylum ap", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Applications", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818225, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63988", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 60420 on Health Services: Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of cancelle", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust: Out-patients", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818208, "askingMemberId": 473, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 60419 on Surgery: Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of cancellations of", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust: Surgery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818267, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-07T00:00:00", "uin": "63986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's policy paper entitled Restoring control over the immigration system, updated 6 June 2025, what steps she is taking to ensure that reforms will allow recognised refug", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818160, "askingMemberId": 394, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "63985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to introduce a national cancer medicines advisory group for England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818286, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps she has taken to promote timebanking in job centres.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Voluntary Work", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818285, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps to promote timebanking to support social inclusion.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Voluntary Organisations: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818269, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63982", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how much her Department has spent on equipment to enable staff to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Attorney General's Office: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818268, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much her Department has spent on equipment to enable staff to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wales Office: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818229, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much his Department has spent on equipment for civil servants to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Northern Ireland Office: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818221, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on equipment for civil servants to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Scotland Office: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818218, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much her Department has spent on equipment to enable staff to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818215, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 30 June 2025 on Nuclear Test Veteran records exercise and the Merlin database, HCWS748, which office the staff that are reviewing (a) the Merlin Database and (b) other a", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Radiation Exposure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818310, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "63976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Minister for Creative Industries, Arts and Tourism plans to respond to the correspondence from the Vicar of Christchurch Priory on the impact of the restrictions on the Listed Places of ", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818301, "askingMemberId": 242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63975", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the Resilience Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Security", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818180, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to limit the use of smartphones in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: Mobile Phones", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818179, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce shoplifting in North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Shoplifting: North East Somerset and Hanham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818178, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the proposed expansion of free school meals on levels of child poverty in North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Free School Meals: North East Somerset and Hanham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818177, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63971", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent progress she has made with the banking industry on the roll out of banking hubs in North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Banking Hubs: North East Somerset and Hanham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818176, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to ensure adequate funding for the repair of council housing stock North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Housing: North East Somerset and Hanham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818175, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent progress her Department has made on reform of the leasehold system.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leasehold: Reform", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818282, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Russia on the airstrike on the Dnipro Theological Seminary of the Orthodox Church of Ukraine; and what diplomatic steps he", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Russia: Ukraine", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818171, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-04T00:00:00", "uin": "63967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2025 to Question 62523 on Shipping: Russia, if she will publish the instructions her Department has issued in respect of the (a) interception and (b) onboard inspection of vess", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1818159, "askingMemberId": 40, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-07-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-07-03T00:00:00", "uin": "63966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the redevelopment of Liverpool Street Station on the surrounding heritage buildings.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Liverpool Street Station", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1818159", "method": "GET"}]}]